Ooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Joker you like that one? Okay. Good. What's up, dude? Hey, I got a module. I'm sorry
I mean a second
How's everyone doing good to see you if you want anyone wants to come up?
Come on the chat. We're I mean, it's an interesting time, right?
Let me get the
Seats which to count okay?
Yeah, that was my death metal song. I do have a finally death metal song the nightmares channel is gonna be like more
You know the side of personality, right?
Oh, excuse me.
Okay, just one second.
You're just chilling, okay, well,
you're always welcome, you know.
There you go.
By the way, yeah, Mr. Extender's channel.
Okay, join around, yeah.
I have another drink right now.
So maybe eight o'clock, okay.
I'll try to be here.
I started drinking a little bit earlier today.
How's everyone doing? Okay, this is Crystal Anne, lady. I mean, it's like, wow. I
Mean the slant like the stuff that they're saying you got a few muffins. Okay. Thank you so much, Joker. I
Mean, I mean and Barb Sawyer and it's like, I mean, I know I know I don't know you and stuff
I know if you're gonna watch this or whatever but
Yeah, before you start calling me pdf and things like that. Yeah, just because you know, you might want to like know
The story for I mean, it's like everyone just a lot of followers and stuff, right? Hey, Yerke, how are you doing?
They're just like, oh this is it's like did anybody
They're so concerned about oh she disabled the chat. Well, you know, no crystal hit me in her chest yesterday for saying hello in the chat
right, right and so
Right and this gamble. I don't know. I mean it sounds like I mean it sounds more of like a
Gay guy that I do right. I mean I may got so anyway count. I don't know this guy who called me
You know horrible things yesterday. You're a monkey. Hi monkey
Well, how'd you learn how to type, you know, he must be a pretty smart smart one, but monkey man slaves, okay
Hey, welcome everybody. This is like actually I like this channel because it's like I get new people
I'm coming in here that I've never met before.
My other channel is probably a shadow band.
A lot of stuff has been going.
So I just, I'm actually, I like this,
I like the vibe here in this channel, right?
Ooh, ooh, ah, ah.
Okay, okay, monkey.
Well, I'm gonna keep an eye on you, cuz.
Ah.
Monkey man likes me, monkey man likes Staky.
Okay, good.
Well.
You're good so far. You're good. You're good me so far. Okay
The crystal I mean, she's literally I mean, it's and Chris Lino if you did have a miscarriage. I'm sorry
I mean, I heard you poured Dr. Pepper in the toilet bowl or whatever. I see the kitty, but um, but I
Mean even barb like when you started talking about baby Oliver. I mean the current like her. She's a rubber baby
rubber baby buggy bumpers
She actually had triplets rubber baby triplets, and I heard she sold her babies
These rubber babies that she had she sold them. I
Don't know
Hopefully they went to a good home. Hey, where's Rudy? You want to see the cats? Okay? Hold on a second. Um, is Rudy here?
Well, you know the thing is I got no, I don't see
I think when we're sleeping and I think I might be out right now, but um, yeah, I do. I'm getting these knocks
Ashante
Perkins, are you the real I show you that are you?
What nudes I didn't first of all, I don't know you have news second of all I
Don't want to see George Floyd's news. Okay
He's not attracted to me.
Anyway, Rudy, I guess I hear the dog barking.
I think they've got the cats with the dog barking.
And also like, you know,
people are knocking my door today
looking for, I guess, today's clippers.
Yeah, I don't know.
Well, Shantae, I think if that's the real Shantae Perkins,
that is an exiled one's wife,
Ron's sister-in-law, and a very rude person.
Oh, we need to knock on the door right now.
We have to get a knock on it.
We're not.
Okay, you know, I don't I don't release nudes. Okay, I'm not the playboy magazine. Okay
Go to chatter bait or something. That's somebody there. I don't know. I don't want to see George Floyd's news. Okay
It'll happen, okay anyway, but yeah
We're having a good day like I don't know it's it's it's
I don't know. I don't know. I used to collect these things called Living Dead Dolls.
They're like these dolls that they've performed in movies.
There was one really scary one, right?
Well, are you Exiled One's husband or wife? I don't know.
I thought it was George Floyd in a wig. I'm so sorry if I'm wrong.
I don't think that's a real one anyway.
Wow, anyway
Regardless, okay, come on panel if you want you can come on panel to the pin the link up in the link here
Let's see oh
Any and then he's like right. Oh, well nobody means but first of all he's not allowed on YouTube
I don't know he keeps it. He keeps he keeps um
Oh, excuse me. He keeps a little looting to the fact that he's like
Oh, well, you know, I'm not a kick, I mean, he's like not on YouTube, I guess, but
Oh
Yeah, I know I should have shared them. I should have shared them. I have news. I mean, it's like I think the only
lesson you know, I got was I think I'm buried the turtle and it was like, you know, probably somebody else's penis
Yeah, but uh, yeah
He prays your beef. Oh my god your beef Wellington. Okay. Well, that now you've gone too far. I
Would say more of like an Arby's Arby's sandwich
but
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. Wow, but um, let me get
Somebody okay. Give me a minute. Let me just uh, I'm gonna show you. I'll play another video. I've made it
It's my last one actually. I think you'll like this one
It's pretty good. Let's see.
Yeah, here we go.
We're the jasmine, wilts, and dust
We're broken prayers, all left like empty cups
No one's talking.
Okay, so we went in and I was like, what?
It's really hard for me to come up with like,
I'm not the most talkative person.
Hey, oh, there's Lola.
Oh, Lola, you wanna come here and say hi to Katie?
Where's Lola?
Lola's kind of happier.
Well, whatever said to the back.
One of them ran away and then the other one came back.
Hey, Lola, come here.
Come here.
Okay, she's walking around.
Come on.
She's scratching her ear with her leg back leg.
Here, here babe.
Hi.
Dressing your back leg? Oh, I couldn't go like that. There you go.
Oh, baby, come on. There's a cat there. I feel like I see a cat.
Hi. Want to sit down? Sit down.
Let's miss Lola
Lola had remember when Lola had we gave birth like she was pregnant
And on north still chase her and I was so afraid like she was like
Not give birth in the house, right?
Yeah
And she's like my little guardian right hi
Oh, is that good?
Are you like that one?
It's really sweet.
You're a sweet cat.
Let me see.
I think I have this.
I mean, I was playing some funny stuff last night about, like, you know,
you watch about Mac and me, but there's this one thing.
Oh, we have a guest.
Let's welcome our guest.
This is Tommy James. Let me see. Oh, okay. Hold on.
Tommy James
What what's the title of your stream?
Stand up for something or fall for anything
more like stand up for
Oh, i'm sorry. I missed it. I'm so sorry. I didn't hear that. I'm so sorry
Gosh, we lost Tommy. What a shame
What a darn shame that was
But
Almost I'm not pretty the way to say how about say how about say it for the truth, you know
What what about tell me James what about I'm great being I'm great being babies again, but you're the jokes you're making
I don't know but you're not banned permanently from the show. So bye
See that's called divide intervention right there when it's just like you couldn't even it didn't even like I mean
I knew what he's trying to say, but it didn't even
You understand. Oh, so it's pretty it's pretty weak
Pretty weak, but how about fall for anything how about fall for any story about anything by this?
Where this gamble is I don't know and I'm not saying anything about gay people. I'm a gay person, right?
But it's like I don't know
Not that gay
But at least he's like, you know, he is like a bitch, but like at least he's like, you know
This is not my straightforward instead of being a two-faced bitch, which he is
most of the time he can go cry on beat us channel and
Do some more lines of meth and fentanyl for
For donations. Let's go do that Tommy. Okay?
Would have rose I would have roasted you to death anyway here, you know, it's like I'm not I'm kind of done playing with people
like you
Go go smoke some fentanyl take a nap and call me in the morning, okay bitch I
Mean really
Tommy James is a bitch Tommy James is a fucking bitch. I know I know don't say that. Come on be nice
Okay, well, okay, so let me find this off. I want to show you a video. This is the time music video
This is somebody else else's video. I think it was Jenny something but it is called like the worst book in the world or something
It's really funny actually and she reads it from this book. It's called
Hmm actually
This is author. I mean, it's pretty it's pretty interesting video that I'll get to when she reads the book. It's pretty funny. Okay. Um,
Oh, excuse me, I
Found it. She found the worst book. Okay, hold on. So her name is Jenny Nicholson. Okay, this woman. Okay. I
Know it's one of her top videos videos
and popular and
Trigger warning so it's called trigger warning
And I'm just gonna slightly speed up the video. Okay
Okay, it's called trigger warning
Mmm
You're dead in here. Yeah, because you're here, but it's all about to be a little bit more dead because you're banned. Okay
I think we did, Katie, I think we did.
I think, I think finally, you know, I finally have, you know,
I mean, yeah, I mean, people are just ridiculous.
I mean, it's like, oh, I'm going to go to this guy's show
and say like something that's just like stupid and untrue.
Cause I am, you know, somebody, just loser.
Okay, here we go.
You know go to your own platform and do the bullshit. It's a bullshit free zone over here
You know it's out for itself. What is this we know
I think it is high time for another bad guess let's welcome our guest oh hold on
a second make sure we have the right person hmm okay I want to put the banner
up real quick I do want to talk to you one second one second cuz I'm about you
I'll try to form. Okay, there we go. Oh, that's what they're gonna do. It's me. Oh, hey, what's up? Hey, hi
How are you?
Yeah, you can oh
I'm on my phone
I can't I can't believe this shit crystal can't stand rejection
You know, and she's just trying and she's crazy. She's using a stupid
Ava what is it AI picture? May you make? Oh my god?
Ella for happily ever after I thought that was and then it was like, you know, it was just crystal
I mean, it's like, I mean, yeah, she just keeps on with the lies and stuff
She doesn't have a life. I guess she lost that boyfriend
But anyway, she was supposed to meet up with somebody else. They said on a panel
Right. Oh, she was cute cute. She's trying to get with Q and he called her out and he called her out
He went off on her. He's not interested
Oh, you have the clip? Yeah, he said he'd rather date me, actually. Did you hear that?
Oh yeah, something about dating you. Who has the clip? What was it on your live?
It was on what? It was on hers. It was on hers last yesterday. It was just like, it was a...
Pretty ridiculous. Yeah. And today she was on Kate's with a stupid AI picture of me. You've seen
my picture. She you know, she's ridiculous. She has no life. I guess she can't get a keep a relationship
and you'll see that because I'll be posting all of those. They're all saved.
All the different guys she takes in. But you know, she's crazy. It's like leave my name out of your
mouth, bitch. I do real life. I had just gotten back home. Oh, I picked a cat tree for my cats.
Oh, you got a catchery. Yeah. Well, yeah, I've never done that before. Usually I get it done. And this was a nice one. And I ordered it from Amazon. So there were a lot of pieces to get together. It's about 57 feet high.
Oh, wow, 50s. Oh my God. Did you have a guy out there? Or are you gonna be able to put that together?
I wouldn't have even did it. I just followed the instructions and I did it. It took me two hours.
Well, that's good. I mean, I'd say I have a few cat trees. I have a room that's basically like,
it has the cat trees in it, and then I have like, so set up, you know.
Yeah.
How many cats do you have?
I have three, and a pecanese, a dog, and I love him.
Oh my gosh, I have four cats right now.
I had a cat, Trix ran away, but he has a brother,
and his brother came back like the next week,
like he's been gone for over a year.
Oh, wow.
It's like, so the cats are like, you know.
Yeah, he's been gone for over a year. Like I had a little
Yeah, these are out from outside that I've rescued and kept
Yeah, they the vet will even advise don't let him out because they can get killed
Anything can happen and that's I've seen a lot of cats, you know that happened to him outside of here
And because yeah, even but you also get him fixed
Please you know because that helps him to the male cats and the females you got to get him both fixed
They are fixed all the cats. Oh my god. Yeah, all of them are new dirt and spade. Oh
Okay, good. Yeah, so I just had that done to the cat that I just took in the one that chose me, I guess
Yeah, she will stay with the other two people that try to adopt her
But I found out after the surgery they said, okay, be sure to shred a newspaper or something and put it in the litter box for him
I said him
Yeah, sometimes it's hard to tell you know it is hard to tell. Yeah, sometimes it is with cats dogs. It's easy but cats is like, okay, because I knew he was acting kind of different plus I was too busy separating him from from my bully cat who didn't want her here, but they're getting along better now and he's still recovering.
But yes, I need a boy named for him because I started to call him Luna
Wow
That's me. Yeah, you has a cat name. I think yeah, Q has if you know Q here
Mm-hmm now
He's pre-poor mom me today and you know, and I have Q Tommy James coming in here saying, you know, P
Yeah, why and then Karen and Barb Sawyer today. Did you see Barb Barb on a on a crystal show today?
I saw her I saw her
Really, I can't believe she's all involved when she knew better. You know, she knows crystal. So all of a sudden she's all, you know
A lot better. She's like, I haven't seen you. I don't like outbreak lately. So, you know, you're fine
Crystal, you know, you're great. But then when crystal started talking about baby Oliver, she's like, well, I know now
Her and baby Oliver I forgot you have this using some stupid
AI, fake picture. I'll use her real ones.
Well, I would like to see baby. I mean, baby Oliver, I mean, if you don't know guys,
you know, she had, well, you know, she sold baby Oliver.
I was told she sold her, she sold her babies.
She had these triplets, the nearly born,
they were there, they were made of rubber.
I remember that, yeah, they gave her a hard time about it, yeah.
I mean, I'll give her a hard time about it
because I mean, literally, I said hello in her chat,
I was blocked, and then she's talking about,
oh my God, Alexandra disabled her chat yesterday.
And how dare, and how dare Alexandra do that?
She do her own lives instead of trying to steal other people's lives, you know recapping
Right. Yeah, I don't know what happened to her because I thought she was actually being really cool and stuff
And I thought really she changed because we all thought that and she's lost every one of us
Well because of her behavior right now
She's trying to be a bully online and going at beta and then apologizes and going at her again
And you know, I mean people are fed up
Well, right. I mean, yeah, you know, and someone said, you know, Regina George or something like that
It was Regina George. You're seeing me. You're seeing mean girls
Oh, I don't know any of those people. I've never heard of them.
Well, it's a movie called Mean Girls with Lindsay Lohan.
Oh, Mean Girls. Yeah, I remember that movie. That was long ago.
Regina George was the head of the popular girl squad.
Like, you know, and so...
Oh, an actress. Okay.
Yeah. I mean, that was the actress.
It was the character's name in the movie.
Remember, the end of the movie, she gets hit by a bus and stuff like that.
No.
But, um...
but it's it but it is mean girls it is like I mean they're bullies um and you've I mean you've seen
that's what she's trying to be because she doesn't do real life she doesn't have real life friends
nothing she's at home I mean there's even a clip of her with captain uh content when she was in the
RV and she was upset because he was playing on his phone uh you know he had filmed her
Holding the phone. She was in discord and it was late at night and she's having a nightmare like she's in discord
She was like
And it's sad because there everybody clipped her doing the same thing even chicken Andy when he was waking her up
She was doing that and he was he was like filming her and he said look
She she's in discord and and has the phone in her hand all night long like she sleeps like that. That's sad
Well, you know me and I mean, yeah, I do almost feel sorry for her almost but like, you know, not quite because she is
Been pretty rude to me and said she can make me cry or something like that
I don't know. I don't know because there's a sweet side to her a caring person. So I don't know
That's the thing all of a sudden she's become like this little monster on YouTube trying to take over and back and forth and back
And forth. That's not the crystal. I was talking to for the last it was like 10 months. Uh-huh
Well, you know, I mean it's like I think that you know, it's I think she's got to get to her head within a week
You know, I think she has to be on for a week and now she's already declared herself the queen of the
Queen of the panel verse or like the Queen she or with King actually she tells us with the King of it, but I'm
She said King she said King. Yeah, I'm not even fucking. I'm actually I'm the King and he was like, oh, don't get carried away
You're getting a little bit carried away with yourself. I mean, yeah, I mean it's like what I know I had hey
What's up? Um, I'll have long a young gam. How are you? I?
Don't know. I mean, I mean I did start
And I mean when I started doing panels, I did have a lot of people immediately in the first week
But it's like, you know
You do have to do a lot of work and I don't but and the gamble guy. I don't I can't stand him
And it's there's a lot of hate but literally all about today is always Andra and and
The barb was saying, well, I was under two PDFs on our panel.
And who in the right mind would, you know, these are children.
Scumbag, Samman's, well, hey, Samman, hey, what's up?
My N word.
Well, yeah, that's a referee.
She's so two-faced, man.
Oh, my God.
Very.
Yeah, and I can't believe that because she, yeah.
Samman's two-faced, too.
He's so insecure because he was like, oh, gee, oh, gee, oh, gee.
Why are you, why are you, why are you harassing Bita?
Leave Bita alone.
Go after Saki, go after Saki please.
And even RG is like, well, like, why, no,
I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'll go after whoever I want him.
We're gonna have to go after Jimmy or whoever.
I mean, I don't care.
But yeah, Sam-Man did a whole,
He's basically almost crying, I think.
I mean, it's like, you have to check out my live yesterday.
Yeah, he says, I'm passionate.
No, that's a mental issue, dude.
It's the internet.
Yeah.
He's all night, all day, they said, and it's true.
As soon as you turn on YouTube, no matter what time of day
or night it is, there he is jumping panels
and getting kicked in most of them.
Right.
I don't have enough, and then it's like, you know,
on YouTube, people usually have content.
but his content is just everybody else's garbage it's like you know i mean he played a card game in
an old video that he made you know i mean that was a different guy you know pretty much a good guy
it's like what does he get back into that well yeah i mean but i but yeah yeah because he was playing
yeah he's playing with his ugeo cards but you know but we do have a i mean any kind of content
because he seemed pretty you know i don't know right now it seems he's doing too much lean
Yeah, I know. That's what it is. Yeah, that's because I do have some pictures like here's some recent photos of him or videos that I
That's him? Yeah, that's him? Yeah, he's playing his Eugeo game and he's...
That's an AI picture, right? No, this is the real, that's what he really looks like though, you know, I mean...
Oh my god, yeah, before now because now the pictures that came out is, you know...
Well, yeah, I mean now because he has he's gained a lot of weight since he's watching I'll just show it really as pictures
There he is. Oh, I think he won. He lost the ugeo game there. Oh, here he is with beta too. He's there's a beta
Yeah, she went to the tanning salon that week or yeah, but yeah very unhinged
But yeah, so he basically saying go after me like attack. Why attack me like me
And I know everyone just like, you know, kind of just feel sorry for him because he's actually retarded and stuff like that. But, you know, I don't know, he has a little, he has a little bit, he has a lot of passes.
So did I hear Sam had a boy, he had a boyfriend when he was in jail. I'd like to hear more about that.
Right, and he's like, oh, he's talking about kids. Oh, there he is. He's in the chat right now. He is gay papa
Yeah, he's gay, you know enjoy I will I will pop us you enjoy
Yeah, I mean
It's not thing is he could be funny though, you know, especially doing other stuff but not bullying or fighting women
I oh I know and it's like and it's like but I believe in some liar when I show receipts even said it
I show receipts. I did learn how to do my my eyeliner
From all the the big troll of streams that he plays, you know, her makeup streams
I do my eyeliner is on fleek. It's perfect now. I mean and so I shout out to the big troll of stream
Or whatever. I mean
But, uh, yeah, same ends, uh, it's pretty ridiculous and to have actually, you know, I do have people coming to my house looking for spoons and, um, you know,
Yeah, this woman came and she's like, I'm here for the spoons.
Right. And she's like, well, I have, there's an ad and I just, I'm talking like they're literally talking on the phone to this person saying, Oh, go knock on the door.
You're going to get your spoons and I don't have any spoons.
the few I had left you know yeah but I mean I do I you know I got thousands of pounds of concrete
I um thousands of pounds like I mean it's like 30 bags 60 pounds each I don't know maybe it's
1000 pounds but my mouth yeah but yeah um um people drive actually they people drive from over an
hour away for free bison a free I'm free metal and it's like I just say I say I'm sorry I don't
But it's really wasting other people's time, like, I mean, I know somebody that he's he's really
like
Hacker he always has been but he'll like fuck with you and spoof your number and call you back when he's pissed off
Or that or then you find your electricity off because he knows how to get you know
To places and shut it off. I think physically, you know, I don't think it's internet stuff
No, it's not. No, no, this is what the people do too. They come out that he's sneaky because, I mean, yeah, he's done that to people. He gets away with all kinds of shit. I needed to contact somebody that there was a friend of mine who runs a rescue.
She needed this person's. What was it? She was taking her to court because she took one of the cats as a foster and it was and she tied it under the bed and it was kind of suffering. So she wanted it back. So I went to the courthouse to file for the cat.
Um, it's just crazy the way people are though. I mean, you know, because that woman was crazy.
I remember she went by the name Demi, but we did get the cap back and I have her missy.
Yeah, and but I had people come to my I like a four in the morning
Oh, I'm here to shut off the water. I had an emergency call
It's like a water company. They come from like about an hour out from emergency water
Yeah, shut off the water shut off the power shut off the electricity
Or the gas, you know, and it's like that is seriously
Illegal and that's why the police started coming and and so I but I have a good relation with the police
My uncle was actually the sergeant of the police department here several years ago, you know, and so
I'm on good terms with them and they know what's going on. They know about the YouTube shit
But it's like it. I mean, but it's hard. I was hard to believe like that people will go this far. It's like this guy
Tony the conductor he's watching right now. I'm sure this guy tell me
and
But luckily, I do have some friends now that know how to find out information and track
them down.
And so, you know, it's like I'm just, I'm at an evidence collecting stage right now.
It's working.
Yeah.
So they can actually get arrested but to keep keep harassing you're gonna do that. Did they are? Oh, yeah. Yeah
I guess that's what I got to do on, you know, who because I had that last a year. No in
And she just keeps on because she can't stand rejection and everybody that's went through this with her all reached out
So this is exactly what she did to them, too
Yeah, he doesn't leave people alone and she has some kind of high anxiety that she can't be out in public
She is a very socially awkward like she doesn't know what to do when she's out there around real people
Right, you know and that's sad
Yeah, and I showed my receipts a call log and all and she wouldn't match it because she knows it's true
It's I mean all these calls that I get from her, but like I said, we were cool. I thought until
She went back to YouTube and there I was back on there too watching bullshit
Right. I mean and uh
Yeah, and
You know, there's this, oh, it's cease and desist, yes.
I mean, it's like, yeah, any kind of legal action,
it's like, that's the only way
that people will pay attention is if they're actually,
but then they feel so, they feel like,
oh, well, this person, you know,
they can't do anything about it and they feel empowered,
but it's like, really like,
But they're doing his felonies. He's attracted to me. It's obvious. I think he might not I don't think he might be
I think he is I think he is
He is I think and how about gamble what do you think of gamble like I didn't know he was a gay guy
I managed like until he heard his voice and then it was like wow
But he said to like a little bitch
I mean he's like oh my god well this and that and oh and this and that and it's really obvious he's like a
In this just bully mindset and I can't sample I mean and that's one of the reasons like why you know
I just was like a little hesitant about believing anything about Brandon's because it's like there's actually the
Like the bullies telling me this or and trying to and then trying to boss me around telling me what to do on my show
I mean if I wanted Charles Manson in the chat
I would have Charles Manson and it's not because I agree with anything, but it's like it would be interesting to have a discussion with him
So, you know reality Nancy reality Nancy's saying saying hello. Oh, oh, sorry. She did it for you. No, not me
We don't get along
Okay, well
I'm sorry. She said, oh heck no. Okay. Well. Yeah, heck no
Go ahead and finish saying
Charles man
like well, I actually I actually
He's starting to talk to dog. Oh, he's so salmon is now threatening the dogs to you
INX he's threatening to dox you right now go ahead he can try because they don't have my dogs
I had that moved and I never gave anybody any information and then that changed my number again
So they can't fight but I got his dogs. So let him know I'll go ahead and show it
I have everything on him everything
He doesn't know that I've had it.
I was just waiting for him to fuck with me
and then I'll show it all.
Okay.
More than he knows that I have.
Right.
It's called like the fuck around find out.
Yeah, so he can shut up about that.
And not only is he gonna be Docs,
the idiot that thinks she has information on me.
Okay, so yeah.
Yeah.
I mean, he said, let him go ahead and try
because everybody's been wanting to, you know,
show him off and everybody know.
Yeah, yeah, but speaking of Charles Manson, I don't know. I do have this. I do have like a look. Have you heard of strip kick?
He's like he's he clips of stuff. Have you heard of him? Yeah, I think so yet trips kick. There's a few trips
trip names, huh?
I think so. Yeah, is he around still well, you know, he's been taken down his channels do
Because you know people will I guess complain about or whatever. I mean, I don't understand why they do that because
He's actually like, you know really funny really fair
but he did do this one
one
Interesting video of me if I can find it. Oh, there's Q Q readers about VB. Let me see
Oh, you know what on my community post shared the video that I shared from some clipper
Glass houses, that's all about salmon. He reported it when I
shared it on my main video page. Oh
So salmon reported your um, it's about yeah that video. Yeah, he did
He reported it, but I shared it on to my
Community post there because it came from a clipper. Look, it's about salmon watch it. It's funny
Yeah, I mean make sure to check that out because yeah, I mean
I mean, I guess he's just, um, he's just
Pack yourself up. That's the name of the account.
Oh, yeah. That's like, you know, I got it.
You came out there?
I mean, I didn't have that particular one, but I did see like
Yeah, Glass houses is the name of the video.
Okay, I'm going to check that out.
Yeah, they're sharing it around. That's how I got it.
Yeah. Um, because
I got a message.
And his family's, um, Facebook.
Okay.
They sent that, all of them.
Like um, I guess I'm tripping sip or let me see let's see. No, no, I got a message about like
Oh, well, Samman is like saying to go after me and it's as opposed to beta or
For calm down. This is the internet salmon. I mean calm down. Damn you were doing good when you first got on
You were popular you were funny and now you're just always going out at women all the time and you don't stop
I post my proof receipts, so stop listening to lies, okay?
I'm not trying to have a war with you.
This is supposed to be for entertainment or fun on your time off,
but you're on 24-7 for drama, and I'm not here for drama.
And this will probably be the last panel I'll be on, Psyche.
Because I really don't need the drama.
And I've spoken to somebody we know that we all respect.
And she gives great advice, a lot of good advice,
because I started getting mad.
It was like, what the fuck?
And she said something that I needed to hear about her
experience and what she's gone through.
Yeah.
So that was nice. And so then I thought, okay, I was going to shut everything off. And then I saw you on. So I joined your panel and I'm going to turn off YouTube.
Well, yeah.
YouTube is I mean it's big especially this community is gets it gets pretty really. Yes, and it continues with us being on
It's like like a good friend of mine told me I used to be pulled in drama and it was crazy
And I said yeah, I remember you I was that was four years ago
And she's having gone for years and I'm happy because she goes I bet they're still going
Yeah, she's right and then when we all go out and have fun. It's like I feel good. It's like why bother with YouTube?
It's like who are these people?
Right except for you and a few other people that you know
I got kind of close with and we're still friends, but not the shady ones that scam people for money
Lie and then forget what they say and I got to remind them
But yeah, but shout out to you
and Alexandra, and I like KK, I respect KK,
the way she handles things.
We're not buddies or anything, you know,
but she's one of my favorite streamers, and Carissa,
I'm sorry, I love Carissa, she's awesome.
Yeah, and Alexandra Meyers. Yes. I'm not saying her name right mayors. I'm sorry
I want to show you maybe I don't know if this will this will take you back a little bit
But I just want to show you this real quick clip. This is um, this is a trip kick a video
I got this one here. So this is a
You know
Yeah, you'll see here. You see it already. Here we go. This is what happened. Oh, they did that
Oh my god that's so funny. Damn, Turp kick to that? Yeah, there's KK Bita and I think, uh, who's that Elton?
Oh, I think that's who. Damn. Oh my god, yeah you make great AI picks. Damn.
didn't he die Charles Manson didn't he die I'm bringing it back and they're
standing right there there's a joker in the back yeah don't leave him on he's
the POS that's so funny they put your face
what's that oh that's cool
For at most for quite you people have done everything in the world to me doesn't that give me equal, right?
I can do anything I want to you people at any time I want to because that's what you've done to me
You know if I wanted to kill somebody I'd take this book and beat you to death with it
And I wouldn't feel a thing. Yeah, it'd be just like walking to the drugstore
You feel blame are you mad? Do you feel like most about rough Venice get fast
There you go. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. That's good. Okay. Thank you. Thank you so much. Okay. All right. We'll talk later. I'll send you a DM tomorrow. So, okay, you have a good night. All right. Bye. Bye. Bye.
I was gonna show you this other thing. This is really funny. This is like I guess this is the worst book ever written
And she's gonna read read from it. You see my history. Okay, but there you go Sam
I hope you got your you know your content or whatever, but you know
You're pretty silly
You silly guy. Okay
Here I'll put this on
This is funny you guys. I think you will enjoy this. This is about
The worst book ever written I guess it's like a true crime to crime book or something
I'll put it on I did start drinking a little bit here too early today, but okay. Here we go
Let's see. I'm gonna speed it up a little bit. Okay
Mmm my frozen I'm frozen. Oh, there we go. Well
No docks and papas papas. No docks and okay. Come on. Okay. Here we go
And enjoy this together. I love this. This is so funny
Trigger warning I'm gonna speed it up a little bit. Okay speed up
1.25
Here we go. Oh
It's negative buzz it's like
Wasps instead of bumblebees for multiple reasons, which I will get into later
I kind of debated whether or not I should cover this book at all
I'll go ahead and say that one of them is that I expected a lot of people to make videos about this book as I was hearing all
The buzz I was waiting for a million videos to roll out people reading it reviewing it whatever
And I waited for that to happen and it didn't it seemed like a lot of people didn't go beyond reading the sample pages on Amazon
This isn't a genre that I usually cover
But I too read the sample pages on Amazon and they were so terrible and I thought they were so funny that I had to read it
trigger warning was written by William W
John Stone with J. A. John Stone
credited underneath as a co-author.
William John Stone is a prolific
author of from what I can tell,
cowboy books. This is not a cowboy book.
Let me read you the summary from
the best selling authors of the
Doomsday bunker Black Friday and
Stand Your Ground comes the explosive
story of a college under siege and
freedom under fire.
political correctness won't save you. That's just all in caps. It's not really part of the summary.
It's like former Army Ranger Jake Rivers is not your typical Pelton College student. He is not
spoiled, coddled, or ultra-lib like his classmates who sneer at the soldier boy. Do they really call
him soldier boy? Is it a reference to the rapper? Rivers is not triggered by microaggressions. He
is not outraged by male privilege and cisgender bathrooms. He does not need a safe space or
Jake's is plural, and when terror strikes, the school needs Jake.
Without warning, the sounds of gunfire plunge the campus into a battle zone,
a violent gang of marauders invade the main hall,
taking students as hostages for big ransom money.
As a veteran and patriot, Jake won't give in to their demands,
but to fight back, he needs to enlist his fellow classmates
to school these special snowflakes in the not-so-liberal art of war.
This time, the aggression isn't micro.
It's life or death, and only the strong survive.
live free, read hard. Uncautiously stoked for this one. I was going to get into the
backstory of this book's publication, which is a doozy, but I decided it would be
funnier if I saved it for the end. So yes, this video has twists. Let's just get
right into the book. Oh, and also gonna add this in before we begin. In case you
couldn't tell from the summary, it does involve imagery of gun-wielding bad guys
inside of a school setting. So if that is just something you find disturbing,
you're probably not going to want to engage with this. So here is your chance
cry in the night made Jake Rivers look up from the book he was reading. To be honest,
he was glad for the distraction. He was on the verge of throwing the book against the wall of
his dorm in disgust. Since it was a hard copy, a thick-trade paperback he had bought in the
university bookstore for an outrageous price. And not something he was reading on his phone or
tablet, he could have done that without breaking anything. Already this is a lot. That's probably
the nerdiest sentiment I've ever heard expressed in a book. From here on the second floor, he had a
good view of the NAFSA Zigger Plaza, the large, park-like area in the center of Kelton College's
Pierce Saul Olmsted and Colohan running north.
I kind of, maybe this is naive of me,
I thought that first paragraph was going to go into him
explaining what was in the book that was frustrating him,
but instead now we're just getting like a mental map
of the layout of the campus.
The administration building was at the northern end,
the main science building, Terrell Hall to the south.
The big Burr Memorial Library was directly across
from where Jake looked out the window.
Knowing the premise of this book,
I assume this whole layout is going to matter later
when he's having to go building to building and save people.
stress, so he goes outside to investigate. It didn't take him long to get down the stairs.
A group of students was sitting in the lobby talking about something. He heard the words
microaggression and privilege and cisnormative. Wow, all three of those words. Just in that
short time, he was passing. That must have been a very concise conversation. Annie, just
be reasonable. I'm not going to let go of you until you start thinking straight. Stop,
Craig. Just stop. The words gasped out as the woman clearly fought to hold back sobs.
I told you it was over. Jake was still moving toward them, but he stopped as he heard what
A grimace tugged at his mouth.
lover's quarrel, none of his business. That was an old-fashioned attitude, and he knew it.
But almost everything about him was old-fashioned, including his dislike of a woman being mistreated.
I guess you could say he shares the sensibilities of a much older man. Of course, if he did step
into help her, more than likely she would stick up for her boyfriend and turn on him instead,
accusing him of perpetuating the patriarchy and the myth of women needing to be rescued.
But she literally does need to be rescued. Why does he just assume that's what would happen?
It's almost as though he's the author of the book and has some incredible foresight
to turn away.
Then Jake heard the crack of open hand on flesh and stopped in his tracks.
He swung around, took several more steps until he could see the two of them fairly well.
She was petite and blonde while the guy was good-sized with dark hair and a short beard.
Bounce like I'm there.
Something was odd about the shape of his head and after a second Jake got it.
The guy's hair was long enough that he'd pulled it up into a bun on the top of his head.
Full respect that Jake is so slow on the uptake that when he sees a man with a bun
he thinks his head has an odd shape.
The guy started tugging on the woman who was actually crying now.
Jake said, that's enough Craig, let her go.
This is none of your business, man.
He paused.
Are you one of the football players?
You're big enough,
but Olmsted's not the athletic dorm.
I like that this other man feels the need to comment
on the protagonist's big news.
Hey, I'm sorry.
I mean, I got a porn bomb by Q.
And so I'll play this later.
I played a porn bomb by Q,
and so I had to end their live.
But if your friend comes back,
I'll read their birthday.
Anybody can tell me their birthday?
I'll read about your birthday.
No that we were watching that she's reading a book. Oh, it's like a really funny book
But that'd be cool to meet her name is Jenny Nicholson. She's uh, she's kind of a big channel, but she's been streaming a while
but
Nancy have ever ever read your birthday?
Yeah
Yeah, he he porn bombed and then because he's mad about this, you know, bq situation
And so it's Tommy James apparently and it's like, you know
Yeah, he did
You know and
Pretty stupid. I mean, it's like I'm just gonna I mean I had to start banning people you wait. Yeah
But you know my birthday is called the day of unusual interest and so you know now you know, it's like, you know pretty pretty accurate so
Whoever throws up their birthday first. I'm gonna I'll pull it up and read it for them if they want
I did start to
What is today? Monday? Yeah, it's party day
Monday it's Monday, it's a Friday night somewhere I guess
But yeah, I don't know before your friend is still here. Yes. Oh, she's still here. Okay
So her birthday is October 7th. Is it October 7th?
I'm gonna read October 7th. If it's not October 7th, let me know I can change it
Okay. October 7th. Okay. Secret language. Okay. Okay. I got it. Did October 7th. Did I get
that right? Okay. Got it. Okay. So October 7th is called the day of defiance. Okay. The
And the report is, those born on October 7th have a strongly rebellious streak, which surfaces sooner or later in their lives.
Those born in the day are strongly convinced of their own belief system, which is more often than not a direct conflict with the mores of the society in which they live.
Their need to protest is often accompanied by a wish to change things positively as they
see it.
Consequently, they often seek to attain a commanding position, giving them the authority
to affect such changes.
Those born on this day are in fact rarely ambitious for personal reasons, but rather
want to acquire power to further their social ideals.
is not always immediately evident on the first meeting due to their often charming manner.
They may seem to be living in the center of their own personal drama, however in a short time
their piercing and insightful views become apparent. Usually they do not mince words on any subject,
saying straight out what they think and often with a large dose of humor
And some degree of tact. They have a good insight into the workings of the human mind and therefore quickly size up
the personal psychology of the individual they are dealing with at any given moment.
Most often those born on this day do not waste time trying to legitimize
their behavior, but simply go ahead and act as they seem most appropriate.
October 7th people
then are very strong-minded. Problems can arise when those born on this day become part of an organization.
Though through the group
Though the group may in general embody the ideals that they themselves support October 7 people must nonetheless to find the role
They must play within that organization as their own principles and politics can be in a process of evolution
Questions concerning leadership cooperation and loyalty can become quite pressing
concerns. Another conflict of October 7th character is between moral and immoral behavior.
Those born this day are not immoral people, for when they sin, they usually deal with
a full sense of what they're doing. But in the world of changing mores, they may not
always have a firm idea of what they themselves consider wrong and right.
Therefore, they must avoid glorifying their rebelliousness while condemning those who uphold the status quo, as they may come to better understand the other side's point of view at a later date.
October 7th people may well say they only wish to be left alone, yet as solitary as they see themselves and perhaps wish to be,
Their fate seems to be thrown in again and again with their fellow human beings, but because they are often considered mavericks by others they may be unfairly excluded by the more conventional in society.
Therefore, those born in this day must try to broaden their base of social contact by actively seeking not only those who whom they wish to respect, but those with whom they can share warmth and intimacy.
So I'm also born on the 7th. I'm more January 7th, and so you're October 7th. So that's pretty cool
We're on we're on the same on the same, uh, you know number of a day
And so I'll give you some advice. It says deal with authority problems improving your relationship with your parents
Be more trusting of those who merit your trust.
Stick up for yourself, don't be a football.
On the other hand, keep your rebelliousness
under control, balance is the key.
A meditation for you is like a baby,
the conscious mind sometimes must be put down
during waking hours.
And I'll also read the health to you.
It says, the health of those born on October 7th
must may have difficulty
functioning well day to day over the long haul.
This can be due to frustration or hidden anger
that can ultimately produce anxiety or depression.
October 7th people must be particularly great,
are careful of feeling threatened
and lashing out in a preventive strike.
I kind of get them before they get me attitude.
Some patterns of stable patterns of diet and sleep,
of course, can have a calming effect
and should be given top priority.
October 7th, people should also avoid overly yin and yang foods, yang or yin foods, like red meat
on the one hand and sugar on the other. So moderate physical exercise is recommended.
Okay, I hope you like that. Yeah guys, so yep. So I hope that, and I did hope that you enjoyed that.
But I have another energy for one more reading if anyone wants one
It is kind of quiet even though there's 30s you people
You know, there might be a lot of some hate watchers at this time, and that's okay
You know, I do have merch hate watchers, so if you're thinking what they can check it out, so
But I'll play that I'll play the other video later
And I don't know, let's see, it's 7.30, so it's very early.
Oh, you'll take a reading?
Okay, Nancy, I got you.
I'll get your cards, I'll get the cards for you.
Here you go.
Here, Nancy, let's shuffle.
She loved it?
Okay, good, good, good.
That's a great book.
Well, the book, it's from this book
called The Secret Language of Birthdays.
It's a big birthday book, okay.
Okay, Nancy
Okay, Nancy we have the Sun and so it's coming from a lot
It's coming from a really good place that got in touch with your inner child like a lot of happiness
Recently also big feeling of being watched over and I would say in a good way. Okay
Also, I would say just
And I would say I would say innocence and that's like a lot of happiness comes from just being in a
Innocent person, okay
Here we go
Okay
We have the I'm actually the fool card. Okay, so the fool coming from the Sun
Okay, I would say this this fool card is like that, you know, you're able to see in front of you
So and also and also in the fool is like not necessarily a fool
But I would say this fool is about especially that Sun behind you, right?
It's like you're being guided in your steps
And so you can feel safe to take the sleep of faith that you've wanted to take you or like there's something that you're
maybe thinking about or considering and
Not quite sure about
Because you know, you don't know the outcome and so you haven't your every day sign in that book. Oh, yeah, so Shan
Yeah, I am I had my friends sign that book too
Okay, you have this nine of one this is okay, so this is like, you know, the nine of it's in reverse
Okay, so the nine of one and an upright would be like, you know, highly defensive. I think that you
are actually, you know, you haven't let things hurt you
that people maybe intended to have hurt you.
And so you have an open heart.
You're not you're not on the defensive automatically and also you haven't let things affect you
Like maybe like people I think I just see like people have tried to
Get to you and they can't they try to offend you or try to bother you or something and it's like you just you're unbothered
Okay, we have a page page of junk, which is the page of pentacles. This is like
Like often like some kind of opportunity maybe with like somebody younger than you, but it's like an opportunity to
It's like I consider this like a seed a seed card. There's like a wish you have
Something that will be able to grow and it's something that will actually benefit you in the physical world
Hey, what's up? Who's who's a zone? You know, no one's interrupting your ear fine. Let me see who is that?
Oh, yeah, you're not interrupting stand. You're fine. I'm gonna pull a few more cards for you
I'll pull three more cards for you Nancy. Okay. What do we have we have? Okay, so this is the we also have the aid of
Pentacles. This is like working on something and actually having the fruits of your labor
Working hard on something
He usually has you know a crafts person that has created something that they sell
I don't know if you're creating things to sell
or some kind of craft, but it's like,
I think this is something that you have enough,
you have it, you've done enough of it,
that it's like you have the credibility
to be an expert in it almost,
and you can sell this, sell and actually become popular.
And we have the three of wands in reverse.
Okay, three of wands in reverse is like,
Okay, so there's like a there's like a there's like a some conflict around you and okay
So in that and it's a conflict around you and it's like and avoid being pulled into the center of it
And I think that this it's a good sign that it's upside down because I think you have avoided
Being put in the center of something that you try to get pulled into to have you be like the
The center of it. Why am I mumbling so much? I'm not mumbling. I'm just I don't know if the microphone is not good
But you know thing that could be like, what's your problem? Why are you why are you such an asshole?
Okay, hold on a few more
Okay, again, you have this ace of pentacles a page of pentacles. I mean this is this is like a year or so
kind of early stage early stage of
Some kind of thing that's gonna make you money. No, I'm not sick. Okay. How about that ample one more car for you?
There it goes two cards popped out
We have the nine of cups, okay, this is like guarding your happiness though
Okay, so at the same time where you're not on defense
You are you you are guarding your happiness. Hey Marcy. How are you? Good to see you?
So Nancy is like this is it's like you also you've accomplished a lot
to put you in a good, really good state of mind, okay?
Happiness.
And then we have, oh, also we have the tennis swords
in reverse, so the tennis swords upright
would be kind of stabbed in the back 10 times.
But this is like, it's like everything missed,
everything missed.
Every knife they tried to stick,
it's like you just like that,
and maybe you didn't see them behind you with the knife,
but every time they tried to stab,
You like went to that you were just you wouldn't picked up something on the floor and it's like they kept missing and so it's like
so it's basically the opposite of of this, you know
Having ten ten things subject subs tabs in your back. It's like you were able to to avoid all that
okay, and
Or we'll be in the near future. Okay, because I think
think there are some backstabbers around you and but just because of your your
good attitude and you worked really hard on something too oh you crave dick I
know you do Sam yeah Sam and you try to catch a fish with that hook right you
give some white dick okay what to eat right or to like you know suck on let's
let's hear about it I want to hear more same one you want to suck my dick
What do you think I'm gonna get bought on this thing?
Oh, okay, I'm so sorry.
Wow, you gotta drink too much.
But Samman City craves white dick.
I mean, I'm not making it up.
He said it.
It's not the real Samman.
Oh my gosh.
Well, thanks for getting my hopes up.
Hey, what's up, money for 20 are you home?
You can give Samman your Greek.
Oh my gosh, see what that could be.
Um, isn't that pink anyways? Hmm. Um, well Barry the turtles was but I don't think it was a real Barry the turtle
But it was whoever's penis. He sent me was black on the base and then
Pink on the top. I
Don't know. I don't know
It's gonna rabbit is coming. I don't know. Yeah, the white dick sampler platter. Just yeah, like really it's like, you know, I
Just uh, you know one's find their dick on the on the platter
Yeah, so anyway, you're welcome, I hope you like that, and I got readings for anybody
that would like a reading if anyone would like one, and yeah, I kind of, you know, woke
up a little bit later in the afternoon, I'm still a little bit, I think I should probably
shouldn't have started drinking so early.
And it's like, it really, it's like two drinks.
And it's like, well, I think I better eat something.
I'm gonna put something on the air fryer,
let's take it.
Right there, guys.
So if anyone wants to come up and talk,
I'll probably, I'll be on for a little bit longer.
My drunk, yeah, I'm drunk, not high.
I don't have any weed, fortunately.
I, maybe, I don't know.
It's like, but now I drink, or sorry,
I smoke so much, I smoke so little weed,
that once I get weed, I just get so tired.
And so I've been trying to avoid it a little bit.
But,
Yeah, but we're having a good night guys with it. What is it is it is?
May 4th. You saw one girl with a bifurcate
By bifurcating dick. I need to look up that name that word bifurcating
Yeah, we have the thing that could be and the same you're out of you're out of air. Yeah, we oh we okay
So what is bifurcating you bi bifurcation?
bi
F u r c a t i n g
It means to divide into two branches or to fork or forks.
Okay. So where did I see that word? Was it in chat?
Well, I don't know. I don't know why I brought that up.
Bifurcating, I don't know.
Oh yeah, there you go. Yeah. Okay.
So you saw, okay.
He saw one guy with a, he had two dicks.
Wow. That is scary.
It was like a lobster claw. Oh big pinchers. Okay. Wow
I
I'll recommend a book. There's a book called it's actually a true crime book about a true story. It's called lobster boy and
Lobster boy had a let me find his name is Grady Styles. I remember exactly
He was in a freak show
But I'll show you what it looks like.
It looks like he's making permanent peace signs, actually, in here's his picture.
Actually, he looks like Tommy James a little bit.
I don't know why, but he does.
You know, you can judge for yourself.
Is this the real Tommy James?
Okay.
Here's Greedy Styles.
The what is the definition of bifurcating bifurcating the definition is to
To divide into two branches or forks, and so I guess
somebody might have I
Don't know
Yeah, okay, so here's the here is the picture of greedy styles
Check out check it out
Downloads desk this up. They get it
Find this picture because this is so this is lobster boy the lobster boy
It's a very
It does look like a young young Tommy James
Like a disturbingly so
Okay. Oh my god. I got it. Okay. I got it. It's in my desk top. It should be in documents. Oh
And chaos, okay
Here we go
Documents
Sam chaos, okay, I know I ended up in there
Our way, so oh here I have and I oh my gosh
You want to see Lola's babies these are Lola's babies and there's tricks and oh my god. Look at these pictures. Okay. These pictures
Yeah, hold me show my screen. So that's when they were born. Okay, you know, these are the kittens
Yeah
Okay, so I'll share the screen because I'll go through these pictures top screen
share screen
Window entire screen window
Hmm
I'll just have to show them like this. Let me see. I'll do the entire screen. Okay. Here we go
So here we go
Here we go, where are they?
Documents, okay, I think it's the second page, okay.
Look at them, oh my God, oh my gosh.
I think they're about two, three sold here.
Oh, this might have been, was this Remy's litter?
It must have been, hold on, one, two, three.
No, that's magic. There's tricks in and there's um, and you know, and
May and may see because I did three the one was a girl. There's four males one girl
Okay, and so let me go back to me. Okay
Yeah, cute, huh? Okay, so let me let me I'll go through it here. Okay, so we see it. Okay
I'm sorry, they're a little bit blurry, but
Okay, yeah, look at the little ears.
Look at those little, getting my,
those little pin back ears.
And then, oh, okay.
So this might have been, okay.
So this was, okay.
So this was actually Remy's litter
because I don't see tricks there.
So, and she had these, look at those little cats.
Like, I mean, it's like, all these cats
were simulated into the neighborhood.
Like, they're a holy one.
There are such, guys, if you've never had kittens,
it's such an experience.
But yeah
Frickin adorable
Like oh, hold on. That's I think that's Lola in the background and she was like I wouldn't have kids too. That's then that was
Yeah, oh no, no, yeah, she see yeah, that's that's definitely Lola in the background there and there she is
You know feeding her babies. Oh my gosh
They were cute little monkeys, huh? Oh my god. Those are the days. Those are the days. They were cute kittens, huh?
Oh, oh, what oh my gosh, that didn't go right. Let me let me end
I'm so sorry, okay. Yeah, you little fella
I know you are your big sexy Rob because that's what little fella says. You got a dynamique. He'll eat my cats. Well
No, you won't because
Yeah, they had the way the white eyeliner. I guess so that thing that that wasn't that wasn't I'm Lola's
Lola had them under the TV set. That was my other cat
And she had two litters actually and so everyone that says oh my god, you had nine cats
Well, last time I when I had nine cats that was because Lola had five kittens and so and I had four cats already
Yeah
Yeah, the kids are so cute and it's like, you know, I just like but it's like it's really hard to
part with them because you know, I
Can't I mean nine cats, but then now people have a problem that I don't have nine cats
They're like why who used to have nine I had nine cats because they're five were born in one day
It's like I had more than double the amount of cats in one day actually, right?
So, but if I had nine cats imagine what people would say your dog's like a gremlin
well you need to do a little bit minion destroyer you do you do you look at your
grub that's you I'm gonna camp on a burger and we'll see how I feel
I might take an early night today
Hey, what's up meaning destroyer? Oh, yeah, I'm sorry. I called you a grumblin. I'm so sorry your daughter's cat about to have kittens ASAP
Oh again again. Yeah, that's that's so I mean it's an experience
Yeah, you went to five kittens that that all ended up pregnant yet for 20 kittens. It was a madhouse never again. Wow
Hey, Joanie. What's up girl? Good to see you. Um, I
Yeah, it is an experience
You know having then it's like and it's really pretty much impossible for me to part with any of them
We have a guest coming on
Hello hey, how are you doing good? How are you? I'm having a chicken burger and yay
Yeah, you're getting fattened up
My third one today. So, uh, yeah, they're really really good though. Yeah, how are you doing good? I'm good
I'm good. I'm glad you're live just cuz I feel like you know, I've been a little bit about stuff
that's
Kind of relevant to your stream. I guess in a weird way
But uh, I'm good. I'm good. I'm having cream cheese wontons
Oh, I love those.
Those are, those are really, yeah.
I even, even, yeah, I love them.
I think I had them first at PF Changs
and then they came out with the grocery version.
And-
Yeah, well, that's what these are.
They're the PF Changs.
You know, you throw them in the oven at 375
and then you feel like you're out to dinner
even though you're at home on YouTube.
Well, I love I'm a cheese person like I I actually I get like I don't I talk to people and I've I said
You'll do you get that serotonin rush when you eat cheese like I I literally will get like
My my like shivers through my brain when I eat cheese. It is really good
I mean, I'm not even supposed to have cheese because I'm lactose intolerant
But I eat it anyway in this supper the next day
not suffer but you know there's but yeah I I mean cheese I mean think about okay so cheese is milk
milk is you know from a cow and you know it's it's a maternal product if you have to label it as such
and it's it's good it probably like subconsciously reminds us of being babies you know in nursing
Product mm-hmm, and I love I mean I love milk. I've never broken a bone in my life
I think I should read it to like me either. I've gotten injuries, but no bone breaks. Thank God
But yeah, I think maybe like I have strong bones because I mean
The generation that we are when we were kids
We were encouraged to drink a lot of milk
so
and have vitamins and eat well.
Food was different than it is today.
Do you remember the Got Milk campaign
where they had the milk mustaches?
Most celebrities, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
What were the big campaigns back then?
Got Milk, just say no to drugs.
Dare.
This is your brand name.
Yeah, it was nice.
And so, we don't have those shirts in school.
But then people that did drugs
started wearing the shirts to be ironic
or something like that or, or, or, or.
Oh, did they?
Oh yeah.
They probably did when I think about, you know,
some little assholes like, I'm going to be contradictory.
Yeah.
And then.
But I mean, I, I like, I went to kind of like this
Eve's drop on a, on a stream tonight.
You know, and oh, I've been eavesdropping. I have I have some of it some of it's hurtful, but some of it is hilarious
You know
well
It's like I don't know these people and it's like yeah, well, it's like it was funny when
I'll say was Crystal Ann and she started talking about just talking to Barb Sawyer
who I
mean everyone everyone that I heard had just even had a problem that
Oh, you you know you blocked your chat or at some point because it was like pretty well that I
Knew the moment well
I was just looking at what they were saying and keep in mind these are people who are never in my chat
When I do my streams, I usually have a very very very small viewership most people watch my videos
Later because I tend to do short live streams. I'm in there, and I'm out of there, but I
usually have
You know, I'd say four to five regulars who as soon as I go live they're in there and like hey, you know, which is nice
but
Then there's some other people but that day that we did that panel
that was like 70 people in the chat and
I was just like, y'all are not normally here.
So you really don't need to be in my chat.
Go back to the realm of the discords
where y'all talk anyway and talk about it there.
And no, you don't get to be in my chat.
And I knew that the moment that I took that chat off,
they were gonna be like, oh, I'm melting.
I'm melting.
And she was one of them, that's why she was talking about it probably, because she wanted
to be in there and I cut her off, but that's how I am in life.
I feel like, you know.
I value myself and if you don't value me,
you don't need to be in my presence or in my surroundings.
Go back to the realm from which you came,
wherever that is.
Right.
I mean, it's like, I mean, I went there and was, you know,
and all of a sudden, like, you know,
horrible things were being said about me,
but the funny part was when
It was Crystal and Barb, I guess.
And then Crystal started talking about baby Oliver.
Can you tell me about baby Oliver,
who I heard you met, baby Oliver?
That's one of the newborn baby dolls, right?
Yeah, yeah.
I think, I don't know what their names were.
Did you help baby Oliver?
I did, I did.
I was not comfortable with that entirely,
but I didn't want her to feel any more anxious
than she already did that day.
And
I mean, I'll tell you those baby dolls do look real, but yeah, and she also had a set of twins
she had three in total and
Yeah, but I never have made fun of her when it comes to that because you know
but that's why I find it odd that she's been so malicious toward me because
I've only been negative toward her in regards to her lying about me. That's it
I have not just been like, oh, everybody burn crystal at the stake.
No, I don't care about that like that.
But yeah, she's mean spirited.
That's just my opinion.
And I'm surprised to see Barb involved.
But I'm not surprised for another reason that.
I'm not gonna publicly say at this point, but I just kind of feel like I know who is
behind a few things
Right and you know, she sold those babies, you know, she sold her babies
She's so what well, I mean was it because there's somebody else who needed one of the dolls and they
I hope so too, I mean, oh gosh, I mean I
Understand why people get those dolls, but I don't really I mean
I'm why didn't she want to keep them?
Those are some pretty expensive dolls.
Yeah, but I guess maybe she needed some extra funds
or something, but I hear she doesn't have
baby Oliver anymore.
Okay, well.
She said, but when she started talking about baby Oliver,
Barb was like, oh, I gotta go.
It was so, it was a, it's a, it's a,
It's a touchy situation, I think, when it comes to her.
I kind of feel, I kind of wish that there was somebody
maybe in her life who could, you know,
help her get some therapy when it comes to a few things
because I think that she needs it.
Yeah, well, I mean, it's like, I mean,
The kettle, you know, I mean, it's like she she's very
They're saying the really horrible things that it's like, you know, you would think that I
Mean the things about people's people having you know, people's babies
I mean, it's like they think you would think that they would not be talking about based on like the other
Other parts of the conversation, right? It's like there's a lot of people feeding into each other right now
Okay, for various reasons, there's a few people feeding into and encouraging Crystal to do what she's doing, some other people to do what they're doing, and I wish that certain people who are being kind of corralled, I wish that they would realize it, but it's not for me to point certain things out, and I'm not going to.
You know
Participate on my own channel when it comes to some things that I wanted to say in some projects
I want to do but when it comes to
That level of drama
They want me to engage really bad. I can't tell but that's why I'm not giving
Sorry, no, because I don't feel like they're worth my time. That's why yeah, and so that's I mean
That's all that's all the attention. I'll give it but it's like
Like really it's like people really are really into projecting on other people their own insecurities and it's and so it's kind of very obvious to me, but
Um, not to them so much and so, but, um, and they want to, well, they want the attention.
They want to play a certain game.
They want the drama.
They want to bring up a certain kind of energy that was at play, you know, what, five years
or so ago now, but times have changed.
People's interest has shifted to other things.
deceased now for several years, those days are not going to come back, and they were only there because he was a very special energy that basically conceived some of, you know, what we're looking at right now, but he's gone.
It was a very, like, I would say just when I saw him, he was just a very.
He was dynamic.
He had an energy that I think started trends.
He was always on the edge of fashion in a certain sense.
I mean, when he was on the red carpet,
there was no denying that he was definitely
about a certain kind of vibe style.
He was pushing some boundaries.
If he had lived longer, I think that he would have probably
someone to go into a level of
either heavy fundraising for a
Really important issue or maybe into politics because he was very quick
Fast fast thinker very charismatic and very socially aware
I wasn't really a fan of his or anything and I wasn't overly familiar with his later music
I do want to take some time to listen to it one day
but
He was before my interest in pop stars like I was into older pop stars
He was on he was like I
Think like ten years back from what I would have seen as like
Trendy or like who I would have paid attention to
But as a person he seems he seemed like he was cool
Yeah, I mean, I mean, it's like but that's the thing. It's like I feel like he was very
Open like it was open hearted person and he like kind of walked into the lion's den a little bit
With the community he went into
Which is yeah, I don't I don't think that he knew what?
Certain streaming communities were at first because it would be hard for him to tell
Because as soon as he would go, you know
on the internet and be publicly accessible
because he was a celebrity,
everyone's gonna be coming at him.
So how would you,
it would be very hard for him to filter
through all the people coming at him.
He would only hear the loudest.
Yeah.
And he had like, I mean, his brother was like, I guess,
Nick Carter, Backstreet Boys.
And so, and then he-
That was the one that I knew about.
I didn't know about Aaron, but I knew about Nick.
Yeah.
They brought him in as like,
I think he was probably 13 or 14 years old
when they started, you know, he came out.
Was he in the Backstreet Boys ever?
Because his brother, his little brother.
His brother, his little brother.
Was he a Backstreet Boy too?
Or was he by himself?
He was by himself.
He was a solo artist, maybe Nukes on the Block because they had Donnie and Mark Wahlberg and then
Marky Mark, literally Marky Mark, but he was in the original Nukes on the Block, which is like
what I remember in the 80s. I remember Nukes. I didn't, yeah, it was one of the brothers who
became Marky Mark. Yeah. One of the brothers of the members of the Nukes on the Block.
I mean, Donnie Wahlberg was in Nukes. Yeah. Then his brother was originally in the band,
You know he started his solo career or whatever and now Donnie Wahlberg is like also Donnie
What was it the sixth sense or something like that Donnie Wahlberg is a big actor
In a certain way now, but I I remember but I remember when I was a kid nukes in the blog
Everyone like there would be um
You know one girl that was a big fan of them and everyone else would say oh, they're gay
and
Like uh because they were the first baby basically boy band and uh
Well, they were the they were the first white ones. I mean you had basically boy bands coming out of Motown
So they it just became pop
Yeah, yeah
They know they've copied the format of that for things a later. I mean, yeah boys to men
Who else was who I mean there there were a lot of
Groups prior, but they were the ones who made it it was you know what it was do you ever see that documentary about their manager?
Who turned out to be a little crazy?
Yeah, but you have to be crazy in the entertainment industry. No one's normal. Come on. I right. There's a lot of
questionable things going on a question like even like the creator of Rick and Morty now it's more of the animation
the creative Rick and Morty is controversial that the Don Schneider from Nickelodeon
Hi Rudy. What are you doing at me? Hi Rudy. Yeah, John Steiner, Nickelodeon. But it's like, yeah, that Lou Reed, they did, he was like, kind of like a heavy set, like, guy in the, and he had all this power to creating this band and, but it's like, I guess they got a raw deal.
I don't think that they had a real money manager at that time.
I think it was more of a on the road act than we may realize, because a lot of bands,
you know, and groups and whatnot, they're basically living a solid gypsy lifestyle and
just trying to perform and get money wherever they can.
before they even realize that they've become famous.
At least that's how it used to be.
Right, and I'm really thinking about like when you say that like TLC comes to mind and they had the famous
They were broke. They were they were broke. I mean, it's like they're they're a record company took like
90 all their money. Yeah, and it is it's like it is like a deal with the devil
I think the record like the little mermaid movie is like a perfect example of like our perfect
for the recording industry
as what does Ursula do? They sign the contract and she gets their voice.
And then their voices go where it's like they can't,
it's like they're not writing their music, right? Everything is very produced and it's like...
Well, sometimes they do. Do you know about the Kesha story and everything that happened
with her and not even being able to perform for years because of that Dr. Luke guy?
Oh, okay. Tell me a little bit about it.
Well, Kesha, Kesha was really one of the final pop stars, I'd say of, you know, the late 90s.
She was kind of primed to be like the next Britney Spears kind of girl.
But
She was in this ironclad contract
with this producer known as Dr. Luke.
And he, I do believe her that he was somehow
inappropriate with her.
And she decided to, you know, try to speak up about it
and get out of the contract and he was too powerful
and basically put the brakes on her career.
And I mean, she's a very well-known artist.
Yes.
I don't think that she ever reached the real level of success and definitely had her
her financial gain cut off by having been in that situation to where she did basically sell her soul
And um, then she didn't play ball
I do the story about work. She asked her fans to send her their teeth her send her their teeth
Have you heard of that story? Really? No, I did not know about that
Like let me see if I can find her real quick because that's like it is an interesting story
It was like, you know, basically, for Keshia, T.
Uh-huh.
Because she didn't act.
That's weird.
Like, what was that about?
Yeah, it says it says it so I found that I found it on grunge.com
It says the truth about Kesha's human teeth collection in 2014
Singer Kesha formerly Silas Kesha checked into rehab for anorexia and bulimia the same year
Her mother revealed in an exclusive people magazine interview that both eating disorders have been going on and going struggles
Okay, then her mother also led the singer's decision to enter a rehab was brought on by weight and appearance matters
Where's the teeth part?
Okay, so it says, according to Refinery29,
Keshia had been collecting and making clothes
from her fans' teeth, specifically a bra,
among other items, as far back as 2012.
I asked them to send me their teeth
and I got over a hundred human teeth.
The singer explained, I made it into a bra top
and a headdress and earrings and necklaces.
I've worn it out.
No.
that that feels a little spiritually ritualistic in some way right well have
you heard of who is there's a singer and I'm just blanking out she's an
African-American singer and she's and I just remember that she she's a rapper
right from the spirit of your name if anyone remembers tell me which one
She has a song about like where she's like Mendoza in the video and oh
Guys, you know
No, no, this is my this is later and she's like a later later artist and but she has a whole thing where she's
She had as I guess she has a room and the floor is covered in in a chicken blood
And, you know, it's a she which rapper is this she's a black rapper. You're you're saying is it
She more is she like a pop rapper or like a hard rapper like like or
She's a hard question. Is she heavy thin? What does she look like?
She okay, so
God why am I blanking out on this guys? Does anybody know okay, so let me look it up. Yeah. Yeah
It's rapper. It's a female rapper who had chicken blood in a music video. Is that what you're saying?
Well, no, she was in her house. She had her room in her in her house and
Azalea Banks is her name Azalea Banks. Oh, I remember her. Yeah. Well, she um, she was pretty open about being into the dark arts
You know, yeah
It says in 2016 she went viral after posting about it
Yeah, it was an instagram video showing her cleaning a closet. She claimed to have been used for three years
Her chicken sacrificed as part of her crew her. Yeah, and so she's a new york rapper and she had a sandblaster
And she's like, this is, I mean, I've seen the video and it's really, really shocking.
I'm very familiar with her and her practices extremely. So she subscribes to a few things
and that's her choice.
Um, right, I mean it's like I don't think that it worked out for her because she was she was on the rise like in a major way for a while and
then
just slowly but surely
things happened and
I
Forgotten about her until you just brought that up
And she does have a really good, I think she has a great video where she's like Medusa and stuff like that. And it's pretty good.
Well, she's pretty. She's yeah, I mean, but there's there are those rumors. There's there's some things about her. I knew a girl who knew her.
And she told me some stuff. So what what you're saying doesn't surprise me at all.
Yeah, in record industry, it's like, you know, they do satanic rituals and things like I mean, it's like even in the in the record
In the studios, I've seen they're pretty open about
You know, especially if you go to certain parties and stuff people are pretty open about
their beliefs. Yeah, what they do and it's big business if actually the people who are
proficient in practicing certain rituals, but yeah.
Because it is, I mean, it's like, and then a lot of people like, I think it's like, you
know, Hollywood and, and fake and stuff like that, but it is actually a real thing.
Yeah.
Oh Selena, what happened so he says what happened to Selena Gomez little fella? She looks like a puppy Brats is all
Oh Selena Gomez. I mean, I don't know. It's really hard. I mean people have a very short
Lifespan in the energy in the entertainment industry. It's like it's a very difficult very rich
Imagine that you have to stay relevant like as long as you want to be popular you have to stay relevant very few
Stay relevant. I mean like
That's why, like, I'm a fan of, like, the actors or actresses from, like, the 90s, early 2000s.
Because they have the staying power, and they worked it, you know?
But now, I don't even really know who, like, the hot Hollywood actors are right now, like, this generation.
well it's all changed now because it's like you know we used to everyone that go to the movie
theater and then everyone would go we watched in the same tv shows at the same time and now
everyone's on a different schedule it's all on demand and it's all and if you want and so everyone's
on a different timeline about it people will watch the entire season of of a series in a day right
now on you you just want you can watch the entire season in like you know eight hours or whatever
Because you get addicted to these shows, and people do.
And so it's not like it used to be.
I haven't seen a movie.
I think I thought of The Great Gatsby.
I think I had maybe Jay-Z and Beyonce in it.
I don't know, but they did a remake of it in 2012.
That was the last movie I saw in a theater.
And then I started streaming. I haven't even watched the TV show. I was a 90-day fiance. Basically, I watched 90. Well, you are the TV show now
You are the show you're the show and one day you won't want to be the show one day, but you're the show right now. So
You know that's what I think happens to like a lot of actors who supposedly disappeared
They didn't disappear. They just walked away, and they were like, you know what? I don't want to be the show no mo
Right, and I think I do think
People fake their deaths too. I mean I have a theory that there's like some kind of like a little small town
Somewhere where it's like there was like a lot of celebrities that used to
And it's like, and then I don't think there's TV or movies in this town or or something where it's like they just retire there
I think Paul Walker, maybe it was one of those people. I always had skepticism about
his death, which was like a
movie steamers, his car burst into flames and stuff like that and no body was recovered and I mean there's like a lot of
interesting. But even if you're celebrity, it's like, what are you
going to do? It's like, because especially the worst thing would be to
be like, I saw like, someone from Full House recently, and they're
asking, Oh, we get great residual checks, huh? Like, you know, you must be
happy. And she's like, Well, this is a sister from Full House, Stephanie.
Jodi, sweden she said well, I she's like sometimes I can pay for a dinner with my
Residual checks they can go out and have it get a bite to eat on them and sometimes it was a little bit better
But she's like now with the streaming
Services that we don't get syndication for that the syndication is all on TV
and so and so everyone's on the streaming services now and so I
Imagine it'd be very difficult especially for a child star
to
Grow up we recognize have the worst thing would be having it's not fair what happened to them
Hmm. It's not it's not right
It's really not right because see I think that the media companies
Have known for a while that things were going to change before they changed us, you know streaming services
um, I mean Roku
basically
came overnight and
Shifted everything right
And you know then I say YouTube followed suit
Amazon so I kind of think that some of these studios and you know media companies did know
But they didn't warn and they didn't care because the name of the game is
The money and I'll say about YouTube right now YouTube is demonetizing and I was demonetized
On YouTube among really yeah among tons of other people
But basically then they say okay go ahead and submit an appeal do a video appeal do a five-minute video appeal edge and
everything and I
did a little you know put some work into making this appeal and
It was not even viewed
Before the decision was made literally within a few minutes or you know within a few hours of
Oh, okay, and and but you know what's happening with the worst part about it is like okay
They're so saying okay, so you're demonetized something your content is not worth anything. They're saying basically, but they're saying
But then now they're putting commercials on my content
Really and I had I when I was when I was monetized
I always had the commercials turned off on everything and some people are like I wanted to see
So you two is actually now monetizing the demonetized channels for themselves with commercials
That shouldn't be allowed I know I feel it's so wrong and I went to I went to Twitter
I took it to Twitter because that's the guy I was told like that's like the last that's
theft. I feel like somehow that's a form of theft. It has to
be.
I feel it is too. And I feel like, you know, I like someone
needs to sue YouTube to do a class action lawsuit about it.
Coming. I mean, if you've noticed it, I feel like, well,
maybe no one has noticed it. Maybe you should talk to attorney.
I don't know if it's in my algorithm, or something like
that. But I do get like,
a ton of people are being them on and it's like anybody that uses any kind of if they use AI voice overs and some of their things or anything and
So anything because it's called in an inauthentic content. They call it and that's what I got hit for inauthentic content
Wow
Because because even though 90% of my show is like the live streams, which are for the original
And it's like I have the 10% where it's like I utilize
AI and the making of
You know what? I have thought for a while with my own media projects that include AI that I should never post anything that's completely, totally unedited by me AI. I never do.
I'm thinking that the patterns of the AI.
might be a pattern that the YouTube algorithm is aware of.
So all it has to do is match up certain patterns with videos
and that's how we can, you know, just like that,
figure out what's human created content
versus AI created content.
So wow, that's an interesting,
You know what? I always said that the AI is going to start to increase the value of the human
strictly human created content
But it's it's happening but it's also
Channels there's channels that use no AI that are have the same because they say there's a there's a show the same problem
Yeah, and then there's channels that are all AI that are fine too, and it's like and also it is an AI that is
Doing it. It's all run by an AI that's that's like so
What's the bias do you think? I think the bias is that I'm right now my opinion is that you too is
You know, there are some channels that are like, you know, they do have some content that is like, you know
Purely people that do voice over but some of those channels are absolutely fine. It's like that's what's really frustrating is that there's
people that are utilizing it as a tool, this is a tool,
and it's like, and then I think it's about money, right?
It's about basically about increasing profits,
and I don't think that they've been very good
to their creators because there's people that put a lot of,
like basically,
So they don't have to pay me, right?
Okay, so it's like, I'll say,
they don't have to pay me for that
because they say, oh, since you're demonetized,
we don't have to pay you for whatever you earned a month,
right?
But then, and then they say,
you can't apply for 90 days for re-monetization.
But then they're like,
if you don't reapply within 50 days,
then we get to keep the profits.
And so, but you can't literally can't apply
Apply within 50 days. You have to wait 90 days, right? And so it's like it seems like a money grab situation. It is really
Really turning me off of YouTube a lot and it's I'm not even afraid to talk about it because
What am I afraid of like, you know after?
What I told you about noticing how someone's being how their chat is being filtered
I was thinking about that today. I was thinking that, you know, I'm going to retain my YouTube channels, but I am going to likely go to another platform and, you know, be consistent with it because there's things I want to talk about that I know are going to be too much for YouTube.
Yeah, yeah, and YouTube is also very you know, there's certain that they say you can't talk about eating this eating disorders
Or you can't talk about
big very random things I'll talk about certain wars going on and stuff or or
Respondization and and so
And so and so I have more freedom as as a not monetized, but I really encourage
creators to like look into like, you know, be sure to promote their cash apps be sure to
Find other kinds other avenues of monetization because
There are other ways besides just YouTube or besides the YouTubes, you know the monetized program, which is like basically
It's I don't even feel comfortable. I wouldn't in the future. You're all I'm always gonna be thinking
Well, is this is this can be considered too inauthentic or or whatever for them
But they also are promoting their tools
They have they have these AI tools that they that they offer now to make shorts and and so they're they're using
it's just very contradictory and
It is it's a game. It's somebody's freaking game and certain people
Um are fucked within the game
Right, it just seems and that's and that's and that's a sad part about it is that you know, especially mild
Mild manner people are people that are like not necessarily. I mean people like anyone can fit people will
Consider weak and it's like in or they can go after them and almost like, you know, try to destroy them and stuff like that and
And then nobody really care.
I mean, that's the saddest part is like nobody cares.
And then it's like, also we do have this hive mind mindset
now where it's like, you can't, it's like where are you?
I'm like knocking on the door.
And it's like, there's nobody listening.
They're not going to change their mind.
They're not going to be objective.
They're not going to say, they're in their emotions.
It's sad.
Artists people may see these most people I think are basically sheep. I'm maybe 90% there. Yeah, and it's like
But you know what there's a sheep in the goats
We're talking about separating the sheeps and the goats and stuff like that and the goats are like these the independent people
and the sheep are the are the followers and it's like
Yeah, I'm just happy I'm a goat, you know, it's like
Me too. Yeah
It's like I
Can't like those are more interesting to watch. Have you ever actually watched goats?
Because I have because I stayed on a friend's farm once and they had goats
They are funny
If you just watch them
They have like they're not like sheep sheep for the most part or just like
And they're happy, you know, and they're cute because they're all fluffy when it's, you know, before they get their wool, you know, shaved off, but goats.
There, goats are interesting to watch. They're goofy, but they're a little stern in a way.
They're they're kind of stern, right? If you watch them and
They said there's ghosts because I you know
I do love ghosts and the ghosts there's ghosts that scream that can scream. There's ghosts that climb
there's ghosts that play dead and
and
Fainting goats. Yeah, there's ghosts that faint, right and
I'll show you this.
This is like one of the most amazing things.
I guess this is Morocco and North Africa.
This is what the goats do there.
Let me see if I can find one really quick.
Okay, well, there's, I see a bunch of goats
and trees right here at home.
So goats climb.
Oh, I've seen them in the trees.
Yeah, they, I've seen the videos of them.
They'll climb the trees and just sit up there.
Well, let me find like a one minute clip of it.
Okay. Yeah. So this is the goats.
They do something else and everything is 15 seconds.
I don't know why everything's 15 seconds here.
But they, so there's these cliffs and there's salt on the cliffs.
And have you heard of this?
This is okay. Maybe I'll find it.
Okay. So I'll find a short clip of this.
Well, here's a goat to find gravity, so let me take that real quick.
So that's a, they're climbing on a possible cliff.
Yeah, so here, I mean, I'm looking for a non-AI one, okay.
Okay, so there's salt on top, yeah, so there's salt on top of the mountain.
This is a National Geographic.
and I'll turn down a little bit because it's kind of loud.
Okay, just check this out, guys.
If you want to see how amazing these beings are,
these, this is crazy.
So here they are climbing this mountain
in order to get the salt on top of the mountain.
I think I got it right here.
Here we go.
You see it?
Yeah, I can see it.
Look at it, look at it. Climb that wall.
Look at that.
It's an inner wall.
Climb that wall.
I think that they just like doing that.
I think for them it's probably entertaining
because I mean, some of them,
they didn't need to be as high up as they were.
But I think that they probably, that's like they're,
you're like, all right, time to climb the wall today.
Let's go.
Oh, the fainting goats.
Yeah, they gotta be, they are a very independent animal.
And...
You know, I think I think Capricorn is an interesting sign because Capricorn is actually if you heard of like
Mesopotamia or like this ancient Sumerian
Mythology, there's a there's a god named Enki. Okay, and Enki is like the god of magic and of the sweet waters
They call him but and he was the Capricorn. I mean, that's that he was like the first Capricorn
and he was and basically the father of
humanity
Yeah, and so there's ancient Sumerian with a goat on it that that's where I think that's where the astrology
Started started. Um, also also, what is it the Mithras? There's a god named Mithras and
Mithras I've never heard of Mithras before. Yeah, let me let me see. I'll tell you a little bit about Mithras Mithras
I think it was an ancient Rome. Okay, and Mithras
It's pretty interesting.
So Mithras, it was a Roman mystery religion, and they were inspired by Iranian worship
of the Zoroastrian Ahura Mazda, and Mithras is pictured, he's in a Phrygian cap, if you
ever seen this Phrygian cap, I'll pull it up real quick, and show you some of the ancient
art about this.
Okay, I got it.
Okay.
Him slaying the bull and they found some they've excavated some temples with this in them and
We see desktop. Okay
So this is myth
Mythorus one second
Yeah, and so yeah, it was it is and uh, I've studied it like a little bit about it
and
It's very, very interesting.
But yeah, he's slaying the bull.
It's second to third century CE,
and it was a mystery religion.
Here he is right here, if you got it, got it.
You know for G and cap. It's kind of like the smurfs if you ever see the smurfs
They were these little caps. I know you're talking about. Yeah. Yeah, here it is right here. I think I got it finally here
You know, okay. Yeah, I'm looking at the Wikipedia for it. I'm just skimming through. Yeah, here he is right there
Yeah, that's what I'm looking at on my screen over here. Yeah. Yeah
And so there's and so that and it's they go I think maybe the word mythology comes from Mithras
Well, it's linked to that Zoroastrianism, which is interesting. You know who?
Proclaim themselves to be a Zoroastrianist who's that that guy that um vegan
Well that guy that vegan patriot was obsessed with Nick. He was into that
I remember him talking about it.
It is very Masonic as far as I know.
If you're, you know, the Freemasons,
it's along those very lines, you know.
Yeah, religion for the for the few right? Is that a INX? Yes, it's yeah
I just want to mention I just saw something from yesterday because I'm not home much
Crystal is a liar. Where where's the proof that I was in a chat saying something about the little kids penis where I mean
She's a liar. Wait, what?
Yeah
Yeah, that that I was in a chat Ganville is believing that he goes tell me what happened. Oh, she was in a chat
It was her and she said something about a little kid's
Weiner it's like a who I I don't think you should even entertain
You know what you're right like that. I'm going to because nobody knows the truth. I've called her out so many times
Look at all my videos
Right.
Just ignore, you have to ignore at this point because I know what they're doing, they're
out of control, they're looking to drum up the drama and I don't want to be in it with
them.
I don't like that.
I just don't.
You know what you're right, Alex.
Yeah, thanks for your advice.
And Karissa, you guys give good advice, yeah, you know, I'm just, I'll ignore it then, thank
you for that because it was like, let me go ahead and post another video, but what does
that do?
It just keeps it on.
You know, I wanted to be the bigger person. I'm gonna ignore it right now. In fact, this is ridiculous
I'm not I'm not entertaining it. You know, I've said what I what I wanted to say and I'm just
because they are they are
Hungry for
attention. They are hungry. Like I feel like they're starving.
Yeah, damn it, especially. They're trying everything. They are starving. And it's like,
sorry, I'm not your food source, bitch. Especially her. Like you said, she can't stand rejection
and she's trying everything she can. She even did that stupid AI picture of me that doesn't
look like anything like me. So that's why I have her real picture on my avatar.
Well, but yeah. Oh, that's who it is. Yeah. Oh, I didn't know who that was. I didn't know what that was.
That was on her IG live when she was going crazy. Oh, poor me. My poor me. Erin. Erin.
That's just that's her. That's her pattern. It's never gonna change. Yeah. Yeah. Okay.
So in her real picture. Yeah. Okay. Well, let y'all continue. I'm gonna go ahead and crash
in a few minutes. I'm gonna vape a little bit. All right. We'll have a good night. You too. You
guys too. All right. Bye-bye. Thank you so much. Okay. Bye-bye.
I know, it's not even worth repeating some of the stuff,
but it really is like, it's like,
really what I did hear was like,
they're not listening to anything anybody's saying.
They're trying to say what they want.
Well, they know, they're trying to trigger people
because I think that they know how to trigger INX
and it did slightly trigger her,
but she's coming down and she's, you know, gonna be cool.
Can tell yeah, I mean it's like that because that's like the best thing that's what the trolls do is they'll find like you know
like whatever
You know, they'll still see what you react to and then they'll they'll double
Yes, right.
And so it's like the best thing to do is like they're like the saying
is don't beat the trolls and who cares?
Like, I don't want to be on their show.
It's like, do I care that?
I mean, it's like, they're sure they would love me on the panel.
Maybe that's why I was blocking the chat.
But at the same time, they were so well, they do want they do want to
draw their enemies on the panel, but then fuck with them.
just to be able to say, ha, ha, ha, ha, you know.
Is that guy Gamble?
But I'm not going on.
Gamble a gay man.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't want to judge, but it's like, it sounded just based on the word.
I think that he, I think that he is publicly straight.
Okay.
Well, okay.
He's had girlfriends.
I think that he was raised primarily by women, maybe.
And I know he mentioned at one point
that he grew up in a hair salon.
So sometimes if you have that kind of background,
it can come across like you're gay, but you're not.
I also think, but I don't know, but but he does have a certain tone about him. I understand what you're saying
It was very catty also like, you know, just catty like
It's like minutes like this as a general attitude and I was
Well, I think that he's I think he's living, you know a hetero
um, relationship because I've heard that he has a girlfriend. Um, but I, a lot of people
have questioned whether or not he's, um, you know, what's going on exactly. But I don't,
I, I don't question. I just think that he's mean-spirited, truthfully. Yeah. And that's
what I think about him. He didn't seem like that at first. I think he's changed. Right.
Yeah, but yeah, he was up there and, you know, very catty and I heard some things that he had to say about me and I was like, really?
Hmm.
So, you know, yeah, but yeah, he does sound like one of the girls, doesn't he?
Yeah, it's it's it's running me like kind of I mean I mean I think I might have sounded like that in high school
High school a little bit maybe but I don't know
Maybe I
Don't know if I'm well my voice deep into something or my balls dropped or whatever
But it's like that. I don't know it just it seems like they're stuck in this
I want to say I want to I don't want to give the compliment of high school because they're like it just seems like
Even more immature than that to me
They want to live out some sort of high school fantasy. That was never their reality
That's what I think
Mm-hmm. Luckily when I was in high school like I mean I went to a very small school
But I was actually like you know, I got invited to the parties, you know the drinking parties
I was actually problem Prince. I didn't room prom king, but I was a prom prince. I looked somebody actually
Yeah, I was cool
Like I was my best friend had a very her boyfriend was kind of like, you know from a different school or whatever and
and
Lot of people didn't like it as well. We weren't we weren't welcome to their hotel room
so I got my own hotel room that night and
And my in their hotel room kept getting you kept and it wasn't my room
but they get that the security kept getting called to them and
and that party but everyone liked my party better that I had in my room and
cool, yeah, and
Gosh, I do have a college degree and I'm college educated
Eventually, I mean, I think I was like 27, maybe 26, 27, when I finally finished college.
I am a little bit, my little brother got a, his bachelor's degree at the same school
I got kicked out of because I was just partying at it, you know, and stuff like that, but
Were you really partying that much?
I started smoking weed when I went to college.
My roommate was like from Chicago, and he like weed and so, and it's like a weed really
It's a I don't I don't know it just kind of it really slowed me down
it was just but I was interested in what's having fun because
At that point I was kind of like my I
Was my parents I was allowed to do I was you know kind of given a lot of freedom in my later teens
But but I was pretty much in a very
Very sheltered
My city had
Very few people I could go you know hang out with or whatever and so I was I was always wanting to go and
Experience life like oh and but that's a capricorn thing to capricorn send the Asian reverse
And so, you know, I was very I was very serious
Serious child very I was at all I did I had no toys all I did it was read books
Um, and you know, well you had no toys like your parents wouldn't get you any toys or
I wanted I wanted books my dad didn't didn't like have an idea that I'd be a college professor
or something like that but at the same time like I was not interested in
Playing with trucks or you know, even I was I was I was I was very you really didn't want the toys
Okay, I thought like maybe you just weren't allowed to have any toys and I was like no
No, I mean I was the good thing about my family is that you know, they let me
My mom was like, I don't you are like a little professor in a way. I do I do my uncle was a
Professor of philosophy at Middlebury College in Vermont and and my other
Uncle my dad's half brother like I picture of him. He's he's presenting the pope with the 63rd birthday birthday gift
I'll share that with you, you know, like there's a
He was a he was a brilliant guy. He was a 16 years old. He graduated from USC like a 16 years. Yeah
he was a he's my dad's half-brother and
And then he went on to like there's like really smart really smart
he went to the New England University of Cairo in Egypt and then he was a he was at Oxford and
Like my dad was always telling me about him and my my dad was like the
You know his so both of his brothers were like college professors, right? And then my dad was like
You know the LA LA guy and
He was a banker and then he got into real estate and his dad was a salesman, too
And and so and so my dad would but my dad was the most successful financially of them all but they were all really super smart
their dog they get my medicals daughter as an attorney and
Like really really smart my mom my mom's side. They were all born in the city by her father and her mother were born on
Redondo Beach, you know back when I had a train station here
there was a train station that was in the city and
And I mean you're like a solid Californian. I think you told me some of that before. Yeah, you're you're like multi-generational
California
fifth generation or something like that like yeah, and I think yeah
For a little further back way, I had an aunt or something like a great
named, uh, I think her name was Rena Rena. Oh, no. Yeah.
It's like the, no, her Nevada, her name was Nevada. I said a Rena, her name was Nevada. Right.
Was her name really Nevada? Yeah.
Her name was Nevada. I've never thought about that as like a female first name before. That's different. Nevada.
Yeah. And uh, so my, my dad was really into genealogy and um,
And also some of the some of the family is too. That's why when I studied the charges of new genealogy
All of a sudden all these pictures started coming up of like, you know, they're back in a model T all the families in a model T
I have to pick it right here. Okay
This is a 1912 and
Let's see. And so there's my that's my
Grandfather right there. It's hard to see it. I'm coming away. Yeah, the reflection kind of blocks the reflection
But there's my grandfather right there. And so they're all in this car. They're all sitting in the car
You can see that's a lot of them in that one car. Yeah
So that's a pretty big car for the yeah, what kind of cars that's funny model T one of the first model T's like
and uh how many people are in that car let's count one two three four are some
of them outside no they're all in the car they're all in the car and then like
wow there's seven eight nine ten eleven eleven people in the car
Oh, come on everybody let's get in the car and they all did get into that car
I would like to see the end. I would like to see the interior of that car
Hey, buddy. How are you doing? Good evening? Good evening, Alexander. What's up psyche man?
I'm I'm the subject of some drama right now, and I don't like it again
Removing myself from it. Do they put you in the pot again that they turned it on?
What can you do just another one Monday just a typical Monday fuck it. Yeah, yeah
Hey psych congratulations, man
Half a million, huh? I
Today I got the notification half a million views on this channel. Bye. Good. Good job
Or I've been done on this channel. So it's on the cult of psyche channel, which I'm half of those are half of those are ghosts and Alex
right
Yeah, most of it is ghosts and no the other the other ox. Yeah, yeah
I know I've kind of fallen out with the other Alex right now because he was calling me. What?
He was couple the other night because you know
I told the story about ghosts was on a panel where they had this woman on and then goes as for her phone number or whatever
And she was, she was 20 years old, but she turned out to be slow.
And, and then, so everyone started going after Ghost and saying he's a PDF now and Ghost called me almost crying and is like, he's like, oh, he's like, I don't know what happened.
His ghost is, we all know Ghost is a little bit slow too, like a little bit, right?
A lot of people.
are slow. I know a lot of people are slow. There's a lot of people who have been at the
center of a lot of the drama that are slow, but nobody wants to say so.
Yeah, but it's like but they're giving such a hard time and it's just because you know, he's like kind of passive
You know, he's like, you know, he's not gonna like I mean he's not I mean he'll he'll fight with people and stuff like that
But then it's like all of a sudden when his friends, but not really friends
Yeah, you know what it is when people like that come up here. It's not like we should give them a special treatment
They'd want to be treated like everybody else, you know, oh leave her alone goes
You know, don't do that there goes. It's what everybody does to each other. We all do that here. They don't special treatment
If that's the case, they shouldn't be here honestly because it's not that kind of environment.
that's what I was saying I was like well why was this woman on the panel then if it was like
because if you're basically saying well she was on the panel but then he asked for a phone number
and then I think she did call the police when he called her or something because she gave her phone
number and oh shit yeah she said to call the police and stuff but I I don't I mean it's it's bizarre
and uh and and I haven't seen ghosts like really since that I think he's really upset like really
Yeah, it is, they're hard on him and because kind of like me in a certain way, which is
like why I almost relate to him is like.
He comes with a kind of open heart in a certain way,
in some ways, he's not a bad person.
I mean, I talk personally.
He's a good guy, but even then,
Alexander was calling him, you're a pedophile.
Like Alexander, and he heard his name.
Of course, that's what he's gonna say about it.
Of course.
And so I was like, I don't give a fuck
about McDonald's or anything.
Alexander, I was like, I was like, get out of here.
Like, and I didn't think.
I mean, I was just like,
and he hasn't been back since or whatever, but.
I mean, it's like he was just on the other day. He's probably watching right now. Yeah. Hi Alex
He's about to come up any second now
Yeah, and I mean he's he's he's watching because he watches you every single day. Y'all talk pretty much every day
He's not I think that
It probably has a little bit to do with the brand and Q thing every that is the that is what's like driving people insane now
right
So Tommy James came up and he's like do you see the title of your stream, which the title
of my stream is Jennifer Stump, yeah, well, he said, he said, did you see the title of
your stream?
I was like, yes, I know the title of my stream.
I named it.
He's like, you know, he can't walk anymore.
And I just came up and I'm going to queue to the same thing today.
And it's like, I mean, it's like, wow.
It was just crazy.
Oh.
Yeah, and then the attack goes because he joins my panel also.
And Charisma, who's a mod in the chat,
they attack Charisma because she's a mod.
I mean, it's like, it is, you know, but like I said,
I'm willing to be.
I mean, I'm willing to even be just destroyed on this channel. Like I mean, I mean it's like at this point
I'd rather stand up for like that's why I said stand up for something. I'm gonna stand up for
Can we set the record straight this is an anti PDF channel
Right, and I mean is there any what I don't understand if there's any pro-pedia
I mean, I don't know if there's a huge movement for pro for pro that you know Sam
Sam's channel is a pro PDF channel. Oh, yeah, you never want to go there
Well, if you want to talk about it if you want to have reach reach hearted
I mean, it's like basically if you heard Sam and Sam and Sam and talk, you know
I haven't even heard what he's been having to say lately.
Well, he was streaming, he was re-streaming me earlier.
I mean, I'm like the, and I was just talking to,
having nice chat with somebody and,
oh, I think it was INX came on earlier
and he was streaming that he has no original content.
I mean, it's like, there's very little original content.
Well, his whole show is about Bita now.
It's all the Bita show.
Bita successfully acquired the Sam Man show.
as their own because it's like both of them are just that they want to be the
super gossipers of the world. Right. That never show their face. Never show their face.
Nor do they have original content.
It's all like, I learned how to do my eyeliner
from Big Trollah, just from looking at same man's stream.
Cause all he does is show six hours
of her doing your makeup and stuff.
And I was like, who is this woman?
I was like, why is he showing makeup streams, bro?
I was still confused for a long time.
I was like, is he doing makeup tutorials now?
No, he just has Big Trollah there, like talking about,
you know, whatever.
I mean, I say, I don't know.
I then I was told it's like oh because he gets donations from talking about it because there's like people that hate her and they
They donate because they hate her and and and so I mean, I think he's about a pair of nikes
Based on just getting me kick off this show or whatever like that. So I don't go on the show anymore
You know, is that what he said?
No, that's what I mean, I just calculated like $200 probably from the eight times I got kicked off for $25 by probably Christine or something like that.
But you know, it's like how much it costs to kick somebody off. Yeah. This is how we're making money in 2026 now. Yeah, I think it's dumb.
I mean, who is he's trying to make a game? Well, he did. He made a game show out of his gossip show.
Yeah, and it's like and I've done the kickoff
I've done that too, but it's like I don't it's not something I push or anything like that like his shows
I was like who's vested who's not and it's because it got too confusing for me to keep track of like
Vests and like it and all that even though I mean, I I mean
Oh, I'm gonna knock at the door. Hold on
Don't ask for it
Who is it?
I don't have a weed eater. I'm sorry, sir.
That's one's having people come to my door and knock on it.
A weed eater at the shower?
I think you, yeah.
Someone came in looking for a weed whacker.
I guess someone's advertising that a weed whacker available.
No, no weed whacker, no bicycles.
I'm sorry, everybody, you know, I mean.
It's fucking eight o'clock at night.
What the fuck?
And no, no, what he does is he goes to Craigslist.
He puts an ad in with his phone number in it.
They call it, and it says free bicycle, free weed whacker.
They call the guy's phone number.
And then he directs them to my door and says knock really loudly ignore the person inside that says no because they're
mentally come at 2 a.m. Oh
I had one guy coming. I thought people come at 4 a.m. Turn off the water and the water the
Gas but they luckily they've come in check with me first
Oh, we're you know, they come up for an hour. They do call the police about it, but you know, luckily I do have
I'll say I'm an ace in the deck in the situation, but I won't say any more than that
But you know, I'm just I'm just the evidence collecting stage right now so I can do it legitimately, right?
So
So, yeah, I mean it's like but this has been going on for over a year. It's just like I know who it is. It's and
It's probably this person also, I think he goes under Lady Bathory. I don't believe that's a real woman. I mean, I think it's the same person.
Yeah.
I thought he was saying Tony.
Tony, yeah.
And also, by the way, and then the other day in your chat, I got a text message right after that show in my phone dead.
No, it's not dead, okay.
So the text message, well, remember I shared that thing where Sandman was telling RG to go after me and I'll read the text message.
The text message said, it said, and it was an anonymous one, it was promoted, it was a channel
called pack yourself up. I think it's bury the turtles channel, but he sent me that link. I think
so too. And he goes, you should watch this. Sandman was trying to get black card G to go after you.
And then he says black card G is a lot worse than allied master computer. Who's Tony, right?
He says he tries to send him around after you around 10.
Or then I guess I was talking about the salmon video. So so salmon was trying to send
RG or RG after me 10 minutes and 30 seconds to 11 minutes, and I'll give RG some props here because
If you watch that clip, where same man starts saying,
stop going to Bita, why are you going to Bita?
Go after a psyche.
He's a weirdo.
He says he wants to F brand and the whatever.
And so that's what he said.
And RG is like, well, he's like, that's not my problem.
He's like, I have my, I have my.
What low cow or whatever it means like I know he's so he RG told him no and then RG was like psyche
You know, they let everyone know he's trying to get people who are going out. So
Doesn't doesn't back out you have a dog named pickles like yeah, you have to worry about him. Yeah, he's not yeah
Yeah, and I try to do I try to do an AI of pickles. I'm moving the other day
I mean it came out like a golden retriever, but this is the best I could do with that. Let me see if I yeah here
I shout out to pickles
There we go. I mean, that's the best I
Yeah, he has a pink glasses. That's all he got. But yeah, I'd have to pick a picture of pickles
That's my my pickles. Yeah, but I did and that was that was my that was the beta and Sam man playing Eugeo and
fighting with everybody and there's a man crying and
Here's some crying again. Here's them crying again and angry
Uh, actually it went perfectly with the clip because he really does make these like, you know
He's he's so angry and um, I mean it's like, oh
It was it was pretty funny though if you guys saw that that uh
that clip by the thingy because I didn't play that yesterday and uh
Where he's telling him go after psyche you go after like stop leave beat it alone leave uh leave dreaming alone go after psyche and uh
Why does anybody needs to go after anybody right and he's not only go after me he's an IRL go after me IRL
Like I guess beta was it was at the same time last year. IRL. Yeah in real life like go after them in real life
Instead of just like you know on the show go you know send people to their house and stuff like that
They need to be careful because you know, they seem to be you know wanting to go out on these conquests
But they don't want anyone to do anything to them. Oh
Bullet they don't know what they're doing
Yeah, I've never been anything, you know anybody just to do anything to them
But it's like they're I mean it's just like he's like oh, why are you talking about kids don't have a kid
Sam is always saying that but then he's doing the same thing plus, you know, I
Same I keep in the chat. He's like, well you oh it's something about Zaya and I was like I think you're like your best friend
Like and he didn't say anything after that, you know, it's like he's trying to like
is it who you know Janet oh Janet there's Janice on around anymore my chat I think she
does her own chat now but I don't think she likes me anymore like there's so many people
that have a boy kind of me by the way I saw bloggers blogger was live tonight he looked
I was like oh who's this I mean it was a skinnier person than me it was it was like I was like
it's okay and I didn't recognize it and I was like what happened he's not okay he's not okay
But what are you?
Yeah blogger come on take care of yourself blogger in a way
And it's like you know you need to make up with your mom or something like that go back to your house
And like don't live in your car like I mean really
If he's being stubborn or something or trying to like, I don't know what he's doing, but it all started
It started with the caretaker. Did you hear when he was ranting about the caretaker? See, I don't I don't really want to
Here's the breakdown
His father is sick likely about to pass
He's contending with all the emotions that come with that.
A caretaker was brought into the household to help with the father.
The caretaker didn't get along with a blogger or maybe blogger didn't get along with the caretaker.
He's done multiple live streams outlining the situation from his perspective
And I think that everything came to a head when there was some sort of a physical fight
Between him and the caretaker alleged was it a guy or a woman the caretaker. Well, he was claiming that the caretaker
was a
trend was it was a transgender and he had an issue with it and he was he was upset about it being
a guy put with breasts and it bothered him and he did a bunch of live streams about it I saw them and
Something happened to where he felt the caretaker
was trying to sneak people into the house.
Cause I think for some reason he was living in the basement
and then like, I guess the main house is above him.
And he was saying that he could hear somebody else
in the house and that's how the physical altercation happened.
Somehow there was alcohol involved in it.
But I think that in the end, his mom asked him to,
Go and you know, if you can't get along you have to get out. That's probably what it was
Oh, yeah, we've seen his mom before there's his one time that he put me on the stream with his mom
All you got to do is ask for a new caretaker and you can just request a new caretaker.
You don't have to keep the one.
I mean I'll share a little bit like you know just a little bit like you know my father
like he um he was basically you know he was sick for a few months but then like then basically
when he was in the bed in his house and then they had the caretakers come over.
My dad loved the caretakers by the way.
like he was like when he was in the hospital I guess he knocked over a big jar of blood or something
like that all over the floor and they came in next scene mopping it up and stuff like that you know
and so that was like and then they also they called him papa and stuff when when they he had these
you know you these gay Filipino nurses or whatever taking care of him and stuff but he'd like them
you know because they were they had really good hearts you know and I do have an affection for
since then because I do like I do like notice that they do have really good
hearts and we had we had a few for my grandfather when he was sick he was
older and there were all these hot Haitian girls so you know I was I was
over there supervising everything right
It was great to be a new one like every other week. It was fantastic
Well, that was like another family friend of ours was also in that kind of hospice and end of life care
And then his wife told me because I'm not saying his name
She told me that you know, he had this an attractive African-American or Haitian maybe nurse come in
and she had high heels on and he just loved her coming in with her high heels and and she was so
happy that he was like at least like happy for a minute when that that nurse would come in
and you know if she didn't care you know she she just wanted him to be like happy you know because
this this time it's like the end you know and so um
Sorry, I mean, yeah
It's not easy it's not it's really hard and it's like I really that that's why I have affection for nurses and
They go through a lot. Yeah, I mean, it's like it's it's not a pleasant
I mean for me it would be impossible. It's like even for the family. It's an impossible thing to think about like doing these
things that the nurses do
They do they do with a smile on their face and they do gladly and sure
That's that's the experience we had a good experience with that and so and it's just like so I am thankful
to those people that
step in. It takes a lot of, it takes a lot of pressure off the
family. It takes a very, yeah, and it takes a special kind of
person to be willing to do that job or to maybe even enjoy
doing, doing that job because you know, I went through that
process as my dad was passing and
Yeah. Yeah. I mean, it's it's basically it was like, it was like the worst time of my life. And
it's like, I mean, I was, I was like, blessed enough that it was just like, it was a couple of
weeks, like two weeks, you know, basically from the time that the hospice care to the end. And
it's like, it could have been a year dragged out, but my dad was like so ready to go, he would,
he refused the medication or anything. My dad was also so sharp, like he
He had his eyes closed, but he was listening to everything
everybody was saying, everyone was thinking he was asleep
and they'd be talking about him.
And then he'd say something.
And then he was always listening.
But hey, I do believe my dad's like,
and this is before I started YouTube.
And I never got the chance to like.
Make him proud or whatever because I was always like the like a big fuck up like
Probably made him proud in some way, you know, I know but he was but he would have been if you would have no one
I've been through a year. I know my dad would be like
Well, I believe they'll see you like I know everyone has their own thought about the afterlife and everything
but I've always been under the impression that
They can see us maybe not like every single second, but but somehow, you know, they can see you're watching over the spirit
Yeah, you can see you. Yeah, and I also feel that it's like they can do things for us in the spiritual realm
That they couldn't because they get to go behind the scenes so to speak or whatever
I think as a spirit and so I do feel like you know
is he's still there like my mom my mom has seen his ghost and she's seen and she it was especially
right after it happened he was there all the time watching her and then I say now he's she's
saying well he's not it he's not as much anymore I think he might have you said your guys are really
Me my father yeah, well my father you know I was I he you know
I got I got evicted from my apartment that he moved me into like you know
I forgot fired and and then I got evicted from there and he he's like you know
Most parents would have given up on
if it was me, if it was me, like, you know,
they would have given up on the child at that point.
My dad never gave up on me.
And then like when I had, I forgot,
I forgot stabbed or whatever, and Glenda,
he moved me back here and the whole family was like,
you got stabbed?
I got stabbed in the ear.
Yeah, I did.
Wow.
And that was like one of the final straws of that living arrangement.
And the family was like, you know, well, don't bring him back here.
Like, don't bring him to the air.
My dad was the only one that wanted me here.
And then when he, so he found me in this place and everything.
Made sure that I would be okay in this place, but he would come up. He would come every week up until up in
He he would if you could have still come even if he was not feeling well
He came at the catheter and stuff like
So like taking a lunch and stuff up to the end like he really he might have loved me so much and
You know, I mean, I'm just thankful. It was really it was fast that it happened because he as soon as he they couldn't like
Be out there because he was very very like I don't like to
Run around and be doing things. He hated being in a bed
so it was it was pretty fast thankfully but
You know, it's like it's still he held the family together basically and it's like a little bit
more difficult now to hold everyone together, but you know I am blessed. I have a great family and
you know I guess next week is Mother's Day and I got to start thinking about that and stuff.
Because I know I'm very I'm very blessed but yeah the only reason I'm still here,
one person believed in me he did but he also made sure and it's like he made sure that I'd be okay.
And so that's why I'm still here like I mean great. You're always with you man. He had faith in you
Yeah, yeah, I shouldn't I don't think I should I mean it's like I always thought I would die at 30 years old
I always had this idea that I was no
Five so I'm already like, you know
But he would have loved I mean he would have loved I mean I did talk to him that I was like thinking about going on YouTube and
And then do me a streamer and like you know, he was very supportive of that and it's like and I know he wouldn't
Like some of the stuff that's going on
With me right like you know some of the people right now, but I do feel like he's able to watch over and
Protect me in some way and yeah
My dad was watching over you who else
Michael that goes down. Michael. Yeah, I remember Michael and Michael is a good guy
Hey, but here's the thing, so it was my niece's birthday like a few days ago,
and so my dad, my dad loved wine, right? He loved to drink wine.
So he would drink it like, we would get a bottle of wine, we had five of us, we had like
my little sister, my little brother, me, my parents, they have seven kids all together, but it was all of us.
And so we would finish up a couple bottles of wine at dinner and, yeah, well I forgot
where I was going with that, but yeah.
But I don't know he was always
So here's what happened. So he would like we would get kind of drunk and we would say oh do your rat face
My dad would go like this here go
We always would print I always
was a really bad rat face and
Do I have a picture of it?
I guess we would have a picture, but my little sister has a couple of daughters and her daughter's
like five years old and she said all of a sudden her daughter started doing the rat face and
insisting on doing the rat face in every picture and she didn't know about this and so my sister
I'll delete this stream anyway, but I can show you.
Hold on.
So this is my dad doing the face,
and then I'll show you what she started doing
all of a sudden, which is like, pretty,
yeah, it was pretty crazy.
They have it, so, yeah, yeah, here it is.
This is my dad doing the face.
He would do the space right there.
That was his rat face.
That's the rat face?
Yeah, with the little hands up there.
Then my niece started doing that in pictures.
Everybody's doing the rat face.
Yeah, she started doing that.
That's funny.
I'll see you do a red face
Yeah, it's like but it's like but it's like that is like little messages like you know you will get these little messages that they are they're
Still like, you know, yeah
You can feel like I feel like I can feel my dad's presence at times. So I think that
That's probably when he's like
No, no, okay, so the thing that is I didn't call you a PDF thing that is I was
Making a point about people calling people that okay, I'm gonna I didn't maybe I did ban you I look at my thing
You know, I didn't mean to do that. I did get kind of like crazy last night, right?
We're doing philosophical discussions, but I was saying that it's like if anybody can be called this, right?
It wasn't like anything personal. I wasn't actually calling you that okay
I was like saying hi, how do you feel when you're called that and it's not true and it's like it's frustrating
And that's the point I was trying to make.
It wasn't anything like actually saying, I know, I know, I'm, I know I got, I know I was silly.
Okay. Hold on. I'll make sure you're on band.
I'm going to say good night because I'm the little Alex.
And thank you.
All right. Good night.
Take care.
Good seeing you.
All right.
Bye-bye.
Yeah.
Bye, sweetheart.
Okay.
Thing that is you're all on hide you.
Thing is it's like I
Was saying anything called anything complaining again. He's always complaining about something. I know
Let me see. I'll find you. Okay. I'm a man. I'm been a lot of people actually think stop complaining, huh?
should be should be
Loser all men loser because people started to people started to turn on me and it's like and start saying shit
And it's like and I and I get
Maybe you stupidly triggered or whatever.
God, do you wanna play the Goddy is God song?
I'll play it for you.
Yeah, do you have it?
Yeah, I have it.
Hold on.
Let me find it.
I got a new one too, if you wanna play that.
Okay, you can post it.
Let me put it backstage alone.
Okay, okay, so oh, I just have a picture of John Goddy.
Hold on, let's see, yeah.
Okay, well, I'll play your new one.
All right, let me put it up, hold on.
Okay.
I'll put it backstage, okay
Perfect because I'll be able to cut and paste it. Thanks Alex for coming on. I know it's like I'm I
Think I started drinking a little too early today, but it's never too early
Yeah, it's it's always five o'clock somewhere, right? Let me see. That's right
Let's see here. Okay. You see you got it. Let me see
We got it. Okay, so let's get the
Here's Gotti's new song guys the world premiere. What time is it 9 9? I have a little bit of time, okay?
I'm gonna grab another beer at the store in a minute, but here we go share
And nobody's ever heard this before. Okay guys. This is the world premiere of the Gotti is God song part two. Here we go
Sorry, dude.
You're a hater.
Gotti, guess what?
What up?
What happened?
Alexander McQueen came into the chat and hit everybody.
Just now?
No, he did it before. He did it on some old show.
He hit literally everybody in the chat.
to make the spin.
Everybody that was a mod, everybody that has ever come in the jet, like, there's 108 people here.
I have to mod him right away.
How many people?
There's hundreds of people blocked right now.
I had like 10.
You sure it was him?
Yes, I'm sure.
I know it's him.
I just know Alex, you know, Alexander McQueen.
You're a little bitch, Alexander McQueen.
I mean, that's your problem.
They literally he hit every single person in this you respect that though. I mean come on
You gotta respect that move. That's a boss move. I would I've done stuff like that before
Are you testing you got it?
I would never test you. Okay. Well anybody that wasn't my guy and hit everybody. Hopefully they'll come back
I mean, it's like
Just extra work, that's all I do that to Shannon's from once
I banned her whole fuckin' chat. I think twice I did it.
She trusted me enough to give me the wrench again.
It's no big deal. Let's say, hey, look, if you got banned, if you got hidden by Alex,
all you gotta do is get over it. It's not gonna last.
It's like he's gonna unban you. You're gonna be back on the show.
Thing, you don't have to cry about it anymore. He's gonna unban you.
You're gonna be back up here fuckin' spoutin' your bullshit.
Don't worry about it, man.
Just go watch a fucking movie or something in the meanwhile Wow
I mean the big guys nobody told me anything like it's like usually they'll still like write to me and say oh
I got hit in us up like nobody wrote about it, but it's like literally he held he kid everybody. I mean it was like
Yeah, I don't know what the fuck is wrong like it has to be it has to have been him
But I don't then I didn't see the name of the model. So I don't know yet
But maybe somebody else but do you think that's why that's why you did you get a bad attitude?
I, yeah, the thing is, you need to improve your attitude right now, hold on, no, no, I think I'm going to look right now to see if you're hidden, but it's like, I, I, I didn't, I didn't get, so I got kind of drunk last night, but at the same time, I wouldn't do, and it's like, so somebody went into like an old, they went into an old stream and like, they're a mod, I went into old streams, let me see what was, I can probably figure it out, so my mods, let me see.
Okay, got that. Okay. Okay. So Joe Shippley, Apollo, really Nancy, Arborger, Gotti, Jamie's Cowboys, 30 diamond, Jamie Rose,
2020, BB
Might have MVP. Okay. I'm gonna take her off the list. Marcy Fox. I know Amber might have been her just Jen
I've been her. Okay
Chanel didn't do it. Okay, Aaron didn't get white dog Rizzer nightbot
Extendo Sharon eraser rain. She and camp hot mess summer
Samantha Avery Barbara our charisma burning joint. These are all mods. Oh, by the way, I'm singing right now
Hey, Miss Liz. Did you like to have Brandon Brandon? Hey there spunky
Page, Duggy, Dug, Tree, Frog, Easy Cameraman.
It's a lot of mods, bro.
I thought you were gonna do it.
It's a lot of mods, but, you know, okay.
So it was almost over.
Katrina won't be saved.
Ivana.
So Alice is not.
Alice and Emma, Queen's not even on the list.
You only need, like, four mods.
Trip and Sip has gone, too, okay.
So, I mean, some people have a, I mean, it's like, you know, Q, Q tried to pour them on
me today.
Then Tommy and James came up and probably tried to pour them on me, like, but, you know, it's
like, there's divine intervention there.
okay well i took off some mott's mean they were born by me channel i don't
think i did that
no no you didn't but that's it but there's over there's a hundred over
a hundred people hidden i thought i had very few people hidden so
be me jams copium dealer sage okay ugly skd okay nor okay nor cal he's gone
i mean i'll embed him but it's a cryptic blue
Troll-troller. I think they were fine. Eric Mercado. So nice to meet you. I mean, it's like what who did this?
I mean, someone someone someone came this morning
I had this thousand mods. It could be anybody had to be the head of in this morning. Oh
My Trevor's hidden. Oh my god. Okay. This is crazy. Like someone came into the literally hit everybody
They could okay, so that's like not good big niches even hit him
We just want just unmod everybody except for me. That's it
Just take a stand
I mean, I'm almost ready to unhide everybody because this is like not right.
I mean, it's like, okay, there's something that is like, okay, there you are.
I think that is, I think it was Alex McQueen, I don't know, it was somebody, I think it
was probably, maybe it was just Jen or, or what's her name, VB, because I was having
a kind of a conversation with them last night, say, turn to his band, wow.
I don't think Alex would do it.
I was in McQueen's not even a funky time. He's not even a mod. I just thought yeah, see so I know so
There are those hidden Arthur was hidden. I didn't hide that I didn't hide all these people yesterday
Oh, I'm gonna do this. I hide a bunch of people
Oh, Lala's hidden. Wow. Lala got hidden
Seventh element see and these people will come J1 got hidden, right? So someone came and hit all my mods
I wish I could see like the the records of who's fucking spooked trying to poke with me
It wasn't Christine. Maybe Christine did under an alt. I don't know. Is she a mods?
So let me see if she's a mods. Maybe she was under an alt
It could be a fake name posing somebody else, right? Okay, so I have one two three mods there
All my mods, Joe Shipley, Apollo, Nancy, Ghost, you,
Jamie's Cowboys, Forty Diamond, Jamie Rose, 2020,
Marcie Fox, Amber, Chanel, Aaron, White Dog, Rizzard,
Mr. Xendo.
Eraser rain
Mr. Extendo that's Joker Joker Joker in this race and not know what you would do it
I mean I'm modern eggs because next is not a good mod. Okay
Let me see I need to unmod some people too. I've on a punch. She's getting unmodded sassy Skarl
It's getting unmodded there are people I heard talking shit about me Patrick in New York is getting unmodded
Christina doesn't even want to be a mod, so she, okay.
Lesk, okay, okay, I think that's enough, okay.
I'm gonna save it again.
Okay, so guys, oh my God, I'm so sorry.
If you were hidden and stuff like that, it wasn't me,
it was just a rogue mod.
I think I got them, I think hopefully I got them out, but.
That's pretty crazy. Like why are you gonna fuck with me? Hey, okay, so it's okay. Did you unhide everybody? Yeah, I had everybody I
didn't hit everybody
So let me see
Timmy with the tool Jared did all the band thing is back
He's back. Okay. You're back. I know you're back. Okay, Irby. Okay. I'm gonna I'm been Irby
I don't see I don't know why these people low battery. I'm been low battery. I've seen Irby in a while
Jeepers, Vanilla Dice Dice Baby, Grendel Inspired.
Untrackable got hidden.
I mean, it's like, this is crazy.
There's somebody with a vendetta.
Yeah, definitely.
Allegedly got hidden, okay?
So easy got hidden, like a friend of mine.
I mean, it's like, it's really crazy.
Someone came in and did that.
I think it was either just Jen or...
You know, I
Don't know but I'm gonna save it again. Here we go
I mean, it's like if you guys if you got hidden and you can't talk in the chat
You can just contact me privately. I'll make I'll look into it. Okay. They can see the whole history
Well, I haven't been gaudy. I miss you. I've been good, bro. You know just taking care of business and stuff handling other things
You care a business. Yeah, you know, yeah, it's a good song
Yeah, I'm I'm trying to take your business too. Let me see
of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those of those
I guess not because it's like that any they don't tell you exactly what it was that
But then they say oh do a you can do a five-minute
Appeals for it on video
That made the five-minute appeal and it's like they didn't even watch it before they came back with the decision
You know what now they're doing they're down there showing commercials on my channel
And you're not getting paid for it. No, and I never I never show commercials. I was
All I had was the memberships on you know, and the whole time
I never had commercials or anything but they now they turn off turn it off and now they now they put commercials on it
So, I mean it's like you should sue their ass
I mean, that's what I'm really feeling like but I'm waiting for a class action lawsuit or something because it's like, you know
I'm me alone. It's not gonna do very much, but it is fucking crazy that it's like people are
Oh, okay. Well, so I think I got it and I'm sorry. I love you. The more you are the better, right?
Well, let me see. Do I have it? Do I have something to show you? You saw these?
Oh, you saw these? Oh, do you see that?
Oh, I'll play with my latest thing. You want to watch my latest video real quick?
Which one? The wolf one? Yeah, play it. No, no, I played the wolf one. This is um, this is the the goddess of the outcast video.
Yeah, play it. Go ahead. Okay. Here you go. I'm gonna play it. Here you go for you.
This is just for Gaudi and for the chat. Here you go. And this is called
Him to Matangi
The goddess. This is called actually, what is it? Something about the unbridled tongue or something like that.
What is it, African?
No, well, she's a Hindu goddess.
Oh, Hindu, okay.
Yeah, so here it is right here. Enjoy. Great back.
That's it. Yeah, here it is.
We're the jasmine, wilts and dust
We're broken prayers, all left like empty
I give them
Thank you so much there was one part of that that was really rocking towards the end there. That was good stuff. Thank you so much
Yeah, I mean I can't believe someone did that to my chat
Like I was wondering why is they only some mods or I only saw it
I wasn't seeing anybody and I was like and hopefully they give me another chance and they understand like it's just people like fuck you with me
Can't you go to an old stream and see if somebody's like just taking people out and do that?
I could have you seen the codex Scotty?
Yeah, your codex. Yeah, it's great. I updated a little bit. You put like countless hours into that thing
I have I actually been working on it since last year and I've done like I had to bleed it several times because it got too
Crazy, but yeah, I'll do you make money off of that at all. Can you can you make money off of it?
Yeah, it's monetized and I have a member
Oh, you have one member, okay.
Yeah, I have a member.
But if anyone wants to check it out,
Codex, you have, as members get access to the transcript,
they also get some kind of editing privileges.
And, you know, you can make your own page
and stuff like that.
Basically, anybody that comes as a member, I will make sure I take care of them, right?
So, I don't know, let's see, we have a thing that is, you like the table and I have your
guitar.
Thank you so much.
Yeah, I mean, basically, I don't, of course, I don't write the music, I mean, I write the
song, I don't write the music, but what I do with the music, I use a bunch of genres.
And I mix them together and then I have it like put it in the perfect way
And so it'll have the elements that I've been I've been once hey once you write the music the lyrics
It's your song. It doesn't matter like what music right to it. You're right
But it's like of course nobody's gonna everyone's gonna say, oh, you know, it's not yours
Fuck that shit, I do
You saw you saw you see the the video with blogger Gotti
Don't think so. Oh, okay. Let me show you this one. Is he is he throwing up? No, this is Alexander made this video
So this is what she made with you and Q going on a date that was really good
Please saw that one. Let me think we have another one to show you wait, of course
I'll just also the beat is BBC that
Yeah, you see them beat is BBC
Beat is BBC the one where she's dancing. No, and I got it for you here. This is a different one here
Oh, yeah, she's dancing. Okay. So you've seen it, but it's okay. We'll play it again. It's old. It's old. It's old, but it's old, but it's brand new.
Okay, yeah, go ahead.
Just play it real quick.
Bita really loves that BBC.
Bita's got a secret, everybody knows.
She's chasing bronze, but wherever he goes,
heart's on fire, she can pull it off.
it out when he's around she can't help but shout out b-touch
that b-b-c it's all she wants it's all she needs
brunt birds the one she can't deny
he's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes
Every word he drops is all she needs Dreamin' bout the day, he'll drive out her way
In her wild wild heart, he's a burning flame He loves that BBC, it's all she wants
It's all she needs, transverts the one she can't deny
He's the reason for that sparkle in her eyes
Vita loves that BBC. It's all she wants. It's all she meets Bronzebergs, the one she can't deny.
The car takes life whenever he goes flying.
That was great. Yeah, I saw that before. It was really good.
It's a classic. It's a classic.
I love when she does those music videos. She's really good at it.
Yeah, she's very good, yeah.
It's like a professional content kind of thing.
It's like my inspiration.
She's like my muse.
You know, it's like...
She's just so she's so amazing Gotti. Can you you feel like hanging out for five minutes talking to the chat or no?
Yeah, I could take care of it. Okay. I'm gonna run to the store get one more dribble. I have this chance. Okay, right back
Yeah, yeah, go ahead. Yeah, you don't have to worry. I'll take care of it
That's fine, okay, you can run run it run it Gotti. Thank you so much perfect. Yeah, you don't worry about it
I'll take care of everything
So what should we talk about yet? You want a positive stream or you want a negative stream?
Let's hear it
Don't take a pole. Yeah, that's right thing. Oh, no, God is in charge the way things should be
You want me to play my song again, I could do that
Yeah, let's do that why don't we do that now I should know I'm too tired for a story
It's too late for that. Actually, you know, I'm just gonna sit here. I'm not gonna say anything
You put the wrong guy up here
It's a good song this is a good song
I've made this song the other day. It was really good. I'm gonna play it for you guys
It's not copyrighted so you doesn't have to worry
I'm so guessed and high and out of here
And teachin' how and when it's not
My eyes become wild and I don't know
I don't know if that's your sign
You
That's you son of a-
there you go kiss from a rose written by me produced by me and directed by me so I hope
you enjoyed that and we'll just sit here in silence until psyche comes back maybe say
a prayer to each other and wish each other good tidings in life only happy thoughts no
Definitely no PDF talk and that's forbidden. No racism
No hate
We don't like hate here. That's why I think that is was actually a band because he's very hateful
Very very hateful guy
I've seen him on a beat as many times
He has this fucking scowl. Oh
It's up there with a scowl on his face. I don't know what happened to him in life. Honestly. I don't know what kind of a
Trauma he's been through
But really he shows it on his face every time he's up on a panel
He has this fucking like a weird inquisitive look all the time like who me like you know like
Like Scooby-Doo when he was like almost our ghost or something. I
Don't know what happened to you thing, but maybe therapy might help
The left therapy in Canada, maybe you can get me through the government somehow you have to pay for it
100%
But we're working on them keep on to be this thing though. I it seems to be helping you big time
Whilst we got down there, what do we got?
What are the fucked up people that we have in the chat?
Shout out to Chanel
We got
That's it. There's nobody else
We got charisma Hernandez. I don't know if that's a guy or a woman
Who's this ice agent
Who's who's you max
You mad good you mad good. Is that a name? What do you like five you mad good? I
Used to make names like this when I was like fucking 12
You just put an X between everything, right?
You mad good must be thing that isn't an alt
Always doing some shit with it fucking psycho. What do I can't see them talk for fucking hours like some asshole. I
Don't do this shit
Like who the fuck sits up on a panel for fucking 10 hours and just talks just rambles about bullshit I
Can't do that fucking stuff. I don't want to do that stuff. I'll die. I'll fucking die. I'll literally die a fucking thirst
My mouth will go dry and I'll fucking drop dead
Shit
My space yeah, it probably was your my space name
Fucking my space
Rob you go way back Rob. I know you go way back like 20 years you were probably on AOL like 3.0
With some lead name
With your dial-up modem
Doing the same shit that you're doing now, right? It's 20 years worth of this shit
30 30 if it goes back to a well
Anybody want a card you want me to pull a card for anybody? Let me know I'll pull a card out of my ass
I got a card for you
Hold on one second, I got a card. Let me get this card. Oh
Shit you've got this card fuck
This is not a good card, man.
This is the clown card.
This is the clown card. This means that you got fucking sad things coming ahead of you.
A lot of sadness in your future, man. You see that he's smiling like this?
That really means that he's fucking crying on the inside because he's covered his eyes.
You see the, you see the streaks coming down from his eyes? Those are really tears.
Tears of like oh shit. Oh, it's like spag. Okay. What are you doing?
Readings over what you get the fucking the ham and cheese you see whether it is subway. It's yeah, it's a wrap
It's five. It was a five dollar subway. They have these five dollar five dollar subway
It's a BLT subway BLT. Hey max god. Hey god
The guy I have a crush on now
What another one? Yeah, I'm another guy have a crush on now
Man you got like five guys in your pocket at all times with the fucks. I don't want either. I want this guy
Look at this get tested. I don't need to be tested cuz I'm not gonna mean to meet him
But look, but you have to check him out here. It's easy and he's on
Okay, I'm gonna pull it up. Okay. There's just his latest post. It just if you look like Chris K forget it
Don't even bother showing me. No, no, he doesn't look at Chris K. Tell me if you think I have a good taste, okay?
I'll be honest. I'll be honest. Honestly. I mean, there you go. Let's share it.
Here we go.
I feel like having a straight man fucking see if a gay man's into another guy.
See him yet? Oh, prison tats. Oh, yeah. Yeah, good choice prison tats. I'll go over that. Look at that.
He'll probably break you in half. I want him to. He was in the chat earlier today, by the way.
He'll split you in two.
He did some of his tattoos by himself. Yeah, that's what I want these you weigh like 98 pounds
Yeah, he'll easily break you break you like a wishbone
Very hard to have him and Chris K. Like rip you apart
That's not my fantasy
I just want one one at a time Gaudi, it's under there's this guy. He's a Cali
Becky's he's like a New Jersey thing. Oh
He's probably got an STD, so you're better off
You think he's married
Well half the guys that are married here, they come up they come on the anyway, so what's the point?
Fucking Michael had a girl. He was gay
and
There was that other dude
What's his name? J-Dog you broke up his marriage. Yeah, are you having fun guys?
Speaking it wasn't my queen who was it who was it was not it wasn't me because there is a thing that is there was
Half the people that haven't been in the show for a long time
So I know that there someone came in and did that hit all the people
But maybe I maybe I didn't hit anything that is but I didn't hit hide everybody
Hey, I think it is because I was trying to talk about philosophical things and I know I went a little crazy last night
We all go a little crazy sometimes, right? The Joker didn't come back. Of course. Let's come back tonight, too
You know, they were having a philosophical discussion. He have whining. No, that's not true. No, no, that's not right. No
Okay, let it go. Let's let it go. Let it go. Let it fly away to the bird. I found him on grinder
No, I found him on YouTube because
No, don't do that. We watch Mac and me. We laugh so hard. Okay, he's smiling. Okay, good
Remember, you know, the thing that is that I wasn't a comedian, Gotti
He said that you weren't funny. He said I wasn't funny and he's like, well, I don't
Yeah, he's depressed
He's usually laughs and smiles at me. He's got beat up by a black midget. Yeah, I'll show that video in a minute
I don't know if you heard what I was saying on your screen, but uh, he's going through a lot of trauma
the thing that is
You had a lot of trauma in his life
Mm-hmm. It's very complain to see on his face. It's that much
BLT yeah, but usually BLT is pretty good. Did you have them put the oil on it?
They put a little oil on it sometimes, but you know what they have like it would be empty and a BLT
The BLT is five dollars. The BMT is ten dollars. What's the BMT?
mozzarella instead of
lettuce
BMT is what instead of let us rather than of lettuce
ten dollars for cheese
Mm-hmm. Five extra dollars for cheese. And then she gives me a cheese. I
Think no BLT. I would I said I would five dollars sub please and she said, oh, okay
Yeah, we can watch the you want to watch Chris K. Get beat up by midget
I think what I usually do I walk I walk into the subway flash my fucking ID real quick
I said, okay health inspector. I'm here to expect you flash your wiener and I was gonna
I expect that I'm here to expect your cheese. So they let me in the back, right?
Oh, I'm looking at the cheeses. So that's when you taste it
I like pepper jack. What do you like? I like that. I'm the one with the not the blue cheese the other one. It's like
No, the provolone the provolone alone. Okay, that's good one of my favorites. It's gotta be the soft provolone. Not that hard shit. I
Do have I think I have this handy it once again
It's like every I've watched it like a thousand times
And I will never get old to me Goddy. I don't understand why this is when he beats up Webster. Yeah, I thought it was Sam
It's not Sam. I don't know. It's not Sam in but it looks like him. Oh, yeah, same height
You can live a very long time
Nobody I bring around here now what
That way! That way!
Exactly! Exactly!
I'm not gonna go to jail!
the sound effects make it right I didn't know that was that would have another one of the
slide whistle less than my brother for a second good shit that's who he makes his money that guy
he goes around beating up the homeless he does terrible good stuff rest in peace rest in peace
Yeah, he died you in here
Who died? He took his own life. Oh, you know who died who died easy you kidding me? No
That motherfucker will be a hundred bucks. How do you die?
Either here yet. I'm not is either withdrawal from alcohol or he got shanked in prison
No, I'm thinking it was an overdose somebody on here was really after his ass
Like every time he came on here, it was somebody was on his ass every fucking time he came. I forgot who it was
Yeah, he'll be defy be used
It's hard Chris K. But yeah, but KZ, you know recipes create KZ. I may find them a little bit not too bad, but it's like
He's like, hey, it's lucky. What was it? It was Bambi. It's lucky. Why is it Bambi? Oh, it's lucky
And then he'd be like so boring and in here it is his microphone. We go brrrr
and he'd be like
Excuse my mark, but yeah, he died in prison recently. I'm that's pretty sad. Oh
Jail jail. He was in jail
Also was an alcohol then I mean it might have been I think he was like you know
I heard alcohol draws, but then RG said he saw the obituary and I heard you got murdered in jail
Yeah, yes, all the police officer before I could say this. I'm gonna say this a lot, but I think aren't you had something to do with it
Don't don't mention that. Hmm. This guy is very fucking shady. It's actually character. Very fucking shade
Do you know who he is? I don't know he is he just popped up out of the blue one day
God you said that's like black RG. Why black RG went on white RG and there was a white RG at one point
Remember that one remember that guy? It's being a black RG. Let me show you this real quick. Something's going on
I don't know what's going on, but something's going on. Is there a white RG? I didn't know there was a white RG
Yeah, there was a white RG. Yeah, just pieces of the guy with the fucking he was playing the he was with the watches
Remember the guy with the watches
Him a candle driestand I'd compare
Oh, yeah, no, that was Randall as Randall Randall. Yes Randall was white RG. Yeah. Yeah. He was white RG
I'll play a few minutes of this. This is like I have a masterpiece I made right here
You're watch this got it right now here we go
Enjoy this
Say I'm an unhinged
You work yourself into a little fizzy
You work yourself into a little fizzy because of something that happened a year ago
And you could be to have a laugh about it many times. You're angry about it. Come on
Come on
Wow you really get the pubic down
Toriel about what happens to be to you try to control
Yesterday I just go real life on beat up over words. Here's the baby. I told you Cinco
I'll get so mad all that, but you don't want me to go through life over you.
Last night, Bita said she was going to dinner with her friend.
You asked, with you, you asked what time, you asked how long she's going to be.
You are controlling the beat of season.
You got called out for it?
Yes, yes.
You act like a chick with a boyfriend, dude.
When you actually go real life, it's a dumb shit, nigga.
Go ahead.
He's not allowed to have friends.
Simple as that.
Go ahead, OK.
You're done?
You've known this for years, and you're crying about it now.
I know.
That's why I'm crying about it now.
A year later.
Why you let Jimmy on your family?
Why you do this?
I didn't give a fuck.
What is going on with you?
Oh my God, don't let Jimmy sleep on your panel, like I'll buddy-buddy with the nigger.
Can you mention my name?
And all of a sudden you're fired up and do it dizzy?
I don't believe that.
226, and we're using the word tizzy on panels.
We're out to do it, my friend.
You asked her who's she going with, how long she was going to be.
What time is she going? That's called controlling, by the way.
You 100% do you try to control her panel?
Who goes on her panel? You don't think Bita doesn't notice?
You don't think Bita doesn't notice that you're trying to control everything about her channel?
Dude, I wasn't the one who called it out yesterday.
You had people on your panel that called that out.
You do everyone else sees it. Why can't you? Yeah? Yeah, that's finally shut you up in it
It happened we'll go watch Peter stream from last night
She said she was going out with her friends
You gave her the whole fucking the whole fucking 20 questions who you go out with you? How long you gonna be?
Yeah, how many people you want with what time you gonna be back?
That sounds like some boyfriend shit to me, but what do I know?
I didn't start this when you said it, and you picked a fight with me this morning.
No, no, no, I picked it up when he started, and I just finished it.
He needs it.
I picked up what Big Ben started, and I finished it, nigga.
Enjoy your meal.
You didn't finish anything.
Enjoy your meal, nigga.
Strange like a monkey.
I'll eat that.
You told me to go to real life, but she's restreaming me right now.
Excuse me, little nigga.
I got to talk on my panel.
It's funny.
Big Ben talked his shit and he want to strike me, but she's restreaming me right now.
Look at this.
Stop it.
What are those?
What are you talking about?
I'd rather stand alone and be a wolf than be so many wolves.
You're not doing this because it's huge, right?
You didn't let juice manipulate you.
It's being a weapon of peace up to 50s.
I don't need it.
All right, Catlin, Capri says, but Samman is too dumb to see this.
Yeah, I don't care a fuck.
I
Even after this song and dance me and beat are still gonna be
Hold it next to that
The entire stream about it. I didn't know never I did not know
That's what we first met
That you win RL on beat up. Never never
Get you that upset to you
That is weak.
Imagine we just took him to a doctor, but you don't seem to be able to get him to work.
This is so stilly.
If he didn't like it, he'd get his weaks and dogs to go to IRL.
He'd get his weaks.
Wow.
You're a weapon.
You're hilarious.
Dude, that's what this is. You're being weaponized right now. This is not new news. I did a stream on it every day
All right, can you be to have talked and laughed about it?
Decided to be team Jimmy and it didn't work out in her favor
All right, now I'm gonna walk it down. Yeah, are you so fired up about our scene Jimmy? How many y'all?
Come on. Now we're gonna. I hated me. You know who kept the real know who kept the real on my
mother that kept the real that came over here. That's a art. That's a art vandalism. That's a
fucking saying. I never said that. I always know what you're doing. If I was cool with Jimmy,
I was gonna dox me. Yeah. Absolutely. Jimmy's not allowed to have friends. We're very clear about
Doxing people for what? For Jimmy. Oh my god, who is firing you up, dude? It's so transparent
It's so fucking transparent right now someone is weaponizing a retard. Don't let yourself be
This is two years ago or a year ago at this point you're acting like just breaking news
All right, I didn't I didn't I didn't I didn't out the shit out take this or don't get mad at me
I did an entire stream about this
Countless times
What are you on about? Is this like are you one yet?
Is this
I don't need to go real life over words
Right, okay. Why didn't you do this a year ago? I wouldn't I would have found out I would have cooked it up too
Trust me. I'll cook it up
You're trying to tell me you didn't know.
I mean, I had a massive following out and then he came for it.
Is that what you're trying to tell me?
No, I'm not elbow. I'm not gonna hit up KK. I still like Sam and I don't know what's up his ass with me right now
This is obviously so using him as a weaponized
Dude stop it stop it
But you're at you're you're at you talk to me like you
Stand alone be a wolf them being so many
You yelling on me nigga, you yelling on me, I gotta, I gotta mute you now, like a little
nigga.
I am into your service.
You're a little nigga.
You're not letting me talk.
So I gotta yell now.
You're a little nigga now.
Let me, let me talk nigga.
I'm a little nigga.
I'm a wild nigga.
Like nigga's finger.
You're being weaponized.
You know what a weaponized retard is?
You're talking.
Do you know what a recognized wreath reads?
No shut the fuck up nigga!
Shut the fuck up nigga! Let me talk!
You said you didn't did it most recent time. I never said you don't beat her
You y'all niggas is getting caught up and y'all niggas is out and y'all some I never put RG doc's beat up
Never said that RG said anything to
I think Kate's whole point is if beta can forgive RG why not her
So Eldo may be right on this one. So, all right, if that's what Eldo's saying,
shout out to Eldo. I don't understand what you're not getting, said that.
Listen, shout out to Eldo now! Shout out to Eldo!
Don't be saved. I'm just reading Chad, dude. This is over nothing.
You can't do this. That's what it is. I'm an old man, nigga.
You can't do this. I'm an old man. That's why I said I'm not a sheep, nigga.
This is what's called recognizing a retard, same man.
Don't think you're fucking talking.
Chateaubo! Chateaubo!
I'm reading a content. Help me to get it.
Chateaubo!
Shane, you're not going to let me speak.
I did what Shane Adams six three six two said I think kids whole point is if Vita can forgive RG
Why not her so El Doh may be right there? I don't know what El Doh said. I'm just repeating or excuse me
Why are you?
I just know Kate was holding next to now and she outed it out because of personal
Entire stream about it. I didn't know never I did not know
That's what we first met
You don't remember that. You win RL on Vita? Never. Never.
She knows what it is.
I don't care.
You're acting like you do.
You're acting weird.
Don't bring the RG on every time I run up.
You're acting like you're in any higher stream.
Vita will get you that upset, so you're gonna go RL on Vita.
I don't care.
That's weak to me.
That's weak.
Imagine me just talking about Doxon, but you Doxon Vita,
but you're gonna take words.
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha!
Oh my God, wow, you're a weaponized re-author, it's hilarious.
Dude, that's what this is, you're being weaponized right now.
This is not new news.
I can't find it, but he says,
Why don't you go to Saiki?
Oh, yeah, it's, God, it's ridiculous.
Go to Saiki now.
Might help.
I ran in queue or whatever.
Hue for mommy tonight, and then tell me James to try to start talking shit about me and I kick him out of the chef
I mean, it's like I don't look at a bad dream just now. I know I know there was a nightmare wasn't it?
You know what you need to do play my song
Okay, we need to go well
Yeah, good play it
Okay, fine. Not the one you just played the the old one
When you wrote the one God is oh, oh, yeah, the God is like practicing AI with remember that way back
Yeah, but I mean, I just have I have that song, but I might have one
I have the song when you hear the song actually I mean I think I made a video of it back you made a video
I can make a video again. I'll make a new video for a new video with all the skills that you possess now
Oh, yeah, I mean it's like I that would take a little bit of time
But this one I can oh don't waste any money on it though. No, I'm like a quickie right now
I can do it and I can do it in probably two minutes. Okay, so um, let me see. I don't put any gait you in there
No, there's no gate. It's gonna be the same song God
God, I mean the images and stuff like that. Yeah, I get it
Let me see if I have it. Oh god. I mean, I remember that I made that. Okay, I have to look for it
Okay, um, what was it called shit? Put a lot of hot bitches in the video like I like you did with the other one
I'm that green bitch you made with the fucking dress and stuff like that
Hey, you like my tongue. Okay, I like skinny girls. I like no skinny girls. So, you know, make sure they got some
Whatever the other cat. Did the other cat ever come back? No, but his brother came back. Is he still with you?
Yeah, his brother came back. His brother's back here. He comes in amazing story. Yeah, it's crazy
He's a black cat. Oh, here it is. This is Goddy cloth. Oh, there's Goddy Claus song
No, that's that one. Yeah, I know I said it's a different one. Okay, then go all the way down. Okay cat
Okay cars and cats crazy. Okay. It's one of my first songs I made. I know it
Oh, it was good, but you've come so far since then. I know I have I have
What's it called? It was called it's like watching a silent film compared to like today's modern masterpieces
Right exactly. It was a let me see community theme song go. There's a ghost song for the Prophecy following
Let's see. I mean, I wish I would have named it. This is Goddy. That would be easy to find. I think that's what it was called
No, I found it one time. I don't let it names it on that when I made it G. Oh, it should be on the codex
It should be I can't find on the codex one dub Queen
But you had a song? I didn't know you had a song.
I don't know. Let me see.
Jebelique.
There was a crystal song, a crystal morning, I guess.
Let me just do a new song. Hold on.
I'm going to do a new song for you right now.
Alright, cool.
Okay, I'm making a new song for you.
Okay, I'm going to say your gaudi.
Are you in a wheelchair? No. No, no, no. Well, it's just tell me so tell me some fun things
Like what are some things we talked about gaudi gaudi is God?
Yeah, that's the first one. Okay
I'm gonna put something in there
Okay, let me think okay. I mean you
Where are you from New York? Okay, New York accent. I'm not from New York. No, I'm in Chicago. Okay, Chicago man
Jesus Christ, dude, what you don't even fucking know I am do you?
No, you write the song. You write the song where you think you know about me, go ahead, write it.
Okay, let me see. Okay, okay. Okay, got it, got it.
Okay, who did you have a fight with? You have a fight with somebody?
I don't fight with anybody. I'm loved. I'm fucking loved by everybody. Everybody loves me.
Okay, and what's your favorite food? You're a Gemini, right?
I like that. Why not fucking Chinese food? We'll just put down some boneless spare ribs. Why not?
What would you say? What kind of food? Boneless spare ribs. Boneless spare ribs, okay. Yeah, boneless spare ribs are good
Can't go wrong with boneless spare ribs
Okay, let me think some more. Okay. Yeah, it's true Chanel I do. Okay. Wow. How do you how do you even know that Chanel?
Okay, so I'm gonna make I said the song's coming. Okay. Here's the song. I have a song. Okay, the song is that song's not printing
Okay, okay doing this song. Okay
This is amazing how fast I do I'm doing it really fast
This is this is a quickie for God because I love this guy right here. Okay, so this is video to
Yeah, I got it. Okay, so I'm gonna put the okay. I just decided the genre hold on. So what's your favorite genre of music?
heavy metal, okay
It's a heavy metal song. Okay. I'm 80s panel. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I got it. I got it. Hey, you got it. Hey, Gotti.
Okay, I don't remember that. What was your answer? 80s heavy metal.
What else? What else do you like?
What was genre?
Yeah, the genre.
Japanese opera. Okay. Okay, I think that's enough of that. Okay. Okay, got that one. Okay. And
okay, so the song is okay. Okay, so another song is printing. Okay. Okay, then I'm gonna put a
video to it. I'm gonna make I'm gonna do a slideshow with it. Okay, so it's generating. Okay. Okay,
it's generating. Okay. Okay, give me a second. One second. Okay. And then I will put it to a
And guys, we're gonna have, guys, it's really exciting.
We have Gotti on the show, Gotti's a cool guy.
I'm excited.
You're excited?
Yeah, this is gonna be a good one.
I hope this is a good one.
I hope it fits you well and stuff.
I try to put as much as I can think of into it at this moment.
This is, you know, this is quick, okay?
This is quick.
It's a fast one.
Okay, as soon as it prints out.
But so what else is going on?
Like, you know, Ziggy and chicken, chicken, chicken.
Yeah, they could put.
Down the house for now
I did this hope for them though. I think those two kids will get back together. Well, yeah
I mean she but she's very she's bad right now, right? Like but uh, yeah
She's bad from here. Well, no, no, she's he's I got she was talking about him today. She's not bad from here
It's like but I left his discord. That's the thing. I left his oh, okay
Ziggy came on he and Mike stroke off or show each other off and they kind of leaving me out of it
And I was like, let me stroke somebody off.
And they said, no, you believe it.
So they're banned from the show forever.
No, I'm just kidding.
Okay, so it's per nail.
Yeah, I am pretty good at it.
I mean, I guess we should, let me see.
In the meantime, in the meantime, should I do?
Well, it's printing out because I'll,
then I have to put the video.
So we'll just take like probably three, four minutes.
So why don't we-
I ate it already. The sandwich is gone. The sandwich is in my bed. It's in my belly. Goddy. That was a good sandwich
so I was I was I
Think I feel tea and years
With that, you know, it's BLC that I think that is standard bullocks that are a favorite sandwich is a PLC. You know that
Let's see. Okay. So, you know, I do you know as a cappy is
Cool, I think happy happy. Yeah
Is it that the guy that predicted that the world was going to end in like fire?
Well, he said that I mean he was a streamer like in 2019 2018
And he thought that he got a message on Facebook Facebook said oh join the Illuminati and stuff
And he thought it was like the real Illuminati writing to him and stuff and you know
But those were both part of it
Let me see but then he and then he but and they went to like this guy's house a
Celebrity and the guy had a bookcase and he's like well behind the bookcase
This is where we keep the children and something he's like
He's like, and then he started going on an anti pedophilia crusade they say that they ever was a PD, right?
But that's what happened there and then what happened?
So I have something good to show you. Hold on a second. But this was an anti pedophilia channel. What are you doing?
It is and it is anti. Hold on. I'll play a you know, he trying to wrote me into a PDF story. Oh, stop it
Stop it. Stop it. I have a I have a you know, God, you like this one. I don't think you've seen this one. It's called behind
Velvet ropes inside closed circles, and I think you'll like this and then I'll put your song because you're you just fucking zapped yourself
What happened? I don't know, but this should be ready by the time you just teleport I'd teleport it
You see me now see it now on screen
I did
Thanks for watching!
They gather where the laughter never reaches the eyes
A circle drawn in chalk where the quiet verdict lies
Every nod rehearsed, every glance a signal flare
If you're not born inside it, you're just passing air
They toast to subtle victories, no one names allowed
A language made of absence, a silence worn proud
You thought it was connection, just a table, just a seat
But the flow beneath you shifted, you were never meant to
They don't raise their voices
They don't make it loud
Crowd in the velvet rooms where the smiles don't bend
Every joke's a sight for every ally's
Pretend close circles home with the low-knowing spark
If you don't read the code, you get lost in the dark
No knives, no noise, just a quiet rearrange
And you wake up one day
Everything's changed
They never say no, they just never say yes
A master class in distance, dressed as finesse
Invitations drift past like ghosts in a hall
You're not excluded, just not counted at all
They study your rhythm, catalogue your tone
Then mirror it back like it was always their own
A soft imitation while they typed in the thread
You're speaking your truth, they're deciding what spreads
It's not what they say, it's what they told
they just need to agree. Consensus is a weapon sharper than a decree. A tilt of a head of
pause. Too long and suddenly you're where you don't belong. No villain declared. No crime
to defend. Just a slow evaporation of where you want to spit in.
So you learn the quiet rules they never explain. Don't show every card. Don't echo their name.
Let your presence be partial. Let your edges stay blurred.
Mystery unsettles what certainty prefers
Not every battle is in a clash or a shower
Some are decided and who gets phased out
Some move like a shadow that knows it's being seen
Not hiding, just never an entirely key
And when they lean in close with that polished disguise
We're warmth in their voice but no depth in their eyes
It's great not like you hear them but who already thought
So, it's great man, like that, okay, that was good, yeah, that was really good.
I was hoping you weren't taking me out, you're just opening a wrapper, okay, thank god.
I'm not going to reach you, I'm not going to reach you to do it, chill.
Okay, well, what's wrong with my video January? Let me see. Oh, no, it's me. It made it made it. Okay. Your video is ready
Okay, let's see this masterpiece. Let's do this. It's a masterpiece. It is a masterpiece. It's coming up
It will come up maybe like less than 30 seconds. But yeah, I don't know
I didn't mean to kick you off the stage just then. It's like you're back. No, I go up. Okay. You fell up. Okay good
Okay, so it's rendering it. Okay, so it is in the process of the so this is gonna be I think I think this is one
I'm masterpieces. Okay, 20% okay. It's almost there
It's good. This is very fast. This is my quick. This is a quickie video
They usually it takes you know, oh, it takes about an hour for me to make a video once I have the
Yeah, he's a little over an hour. Don't do that for you. Yeah, but this is a quickie. So this is the five minute one
But this is the gaudy saw
And, uh, 80%, okay, the 80%, so this is like the last stage, and then I'll be able to save it and put it on.
Okay, guys.
I think this is going to be great.
World premiere of the, this is called Gaudi, Gaudi Part 2.
That's what I'm going to name it, Gaudi Part 2.
That Reese's is good.
You ever have Reese's?
I love Reese's.
I love, I do love Reese's.
It's not the cup.
It was a fast one.
I like Reese's pieces.
Is that what they are?
Oh, the Reese's piece. I remember those those are good. They're good. Hey, the video's ready guys. I hate them in them
So I know and the video is ready though. Let's watch it. Okay, you ready for it?
Are you ready? Well, let's go chop chop. No, no. Okay. Okay. Okay. One second and
It is ready. Okay. So here it is guys the world premiere of the gaudy video, right and
Enjoy 0
I love it already
I'm fucking speechless man. That was great. Well, you got everything in there, right? Everything about my life was in there.
Fucking beautiful
What a tribute man. Thank you, bro
Guys guys
Come on up. I mean that was fucking sick. Come on. Donate everyone donate to the show. That was a great video. He didn't have to do that
Come on reaching your targets. Come on. That's at least good for 20. Come on, Jody
Oh God, we're all doing good. Oh my gosh.
What I said, I said no wheelchair, right?
I had to put it in. I had to put it in.
I made it at the focal point.
I had the wheelchair in the alley.
I like when the wheelchair was going down the graffiti alley.
That was, yeah.
Joni's done.
I think Joni's done with me.
Joni slightly tolerates me at this point.
I think I'm on the gnaw you list right now.
She came at the office.
Okay. Yeah.
Oh, white dog out the wheelchair thing. Yeah, it's like he hates people that are disabled. So he just
Knows that I was in a wheelchair for eight years and he always fucking gives me shit for it. Oh, yeah
I think we might have a guest coming up
Was a good guest or a bad guest, I think it's a great surprise
I think you'll be happy
But yeah, so it's an interesting time. Have you watched Alexander's Streams lately? Have you seen like any of the
Controversy or anything going on? I don't know. I've seen something about uh, was it Trishalicious or something like that?
Yeah, Trishalicious, like now Trishalicious. What was that all about?
Trishalicious has turned on her and it's like, you know
And it's like thinking like oh Alice is like you know cuz Alex don't need to somebody and she's like, you know
Oh, here we go every guest coming up. Let's talk
Joanie Bologna
Mm-hmm. There she is.
Joni, booby, baby. How you doing, baby doll?
Booby, booby, booby, booby, baby.
Make me, make me.
Never make you. We can never make you.
Just fucking make me.
Did she say make or bake?
Bake and make.
I'm making bake.
Easy bake, huh?
What's going on, doll?
Why does that laugh?
Is that wicked laugh?
Maybe she's slapping the flesh already.
I was coming up with like fucking angst, but now you got me laughing don't do it
How you been? No
I will not be ignored
Wait, let me look do you say mole or mole what?
mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold mold
I wanted to be mad so mad at you and now you made me laugh. How dare you how dare you be mad at me?
What I dare you?
She's mad at you
I didn't even mad
It ain't mad
Life's too short to be sorry, excuse me. I just had a spin a little sudden at the side of the floor
So funny, I almost farted and laughed at the same time.
There's a movie, there was a movie with Bob Hope.
Movie, what?
Like, you know this movie.
There's a movie with Bob Hope and Phyllis Diller
where he was cheating on his wife.
You ever see that movie?
I think it was Doris Day, Doris Day was in it.
And Phyllis Diller was in the fucking bubble bath
with the fucking bubbles and everything.
Joni is laughing just like Phil's, you remind me of Phil's still enjoying.
Thank you very much. Same hair, same hair.
It's called, it's a brief but notable affair.
Yes, that's the one, that's the one.
Was the door staying? Was it her?
Yeah, it was Doris Day
You're trying to pin me into a song and I won't do it unless I mean, you know, I'm saying I could easily do a show too
I mean, that's my hey listen. No, maybe make me if you sing this thing
Listen listen
I am not high, fucker.
She is, look at that wig.
She was a beauty, wasn't she?
Look at that, when Joni laughs,
it still is fucking laughing.
She was the white Tina Turner.
Suck my dick if I only had one.
I swear that I would, you know what to do with it.
I'm like you boys.
And it's not ladylike, it's a terrible thing.
It's a terrible thing, it is.
Wow.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh, oh.
Ah!
I think Miss Diller's laugh is the greatest laugh in history.
It just cracked me up since I was a little girl and would hear her comedy records.
I'm singing again.
I finally recovered from that terrible singing accident.
What singing accident?
From that little star-spangled banner.
We're both cut from the same mold.
It's just that I'm moldy.
I'm moldy.
My first being at Hollywood, I could have had a problem.
You know, because you have the microphone, right?
This is your channel, you're a street.
I don't think there's been problems.
You do, you know, boo!
It's so small, it had to be put on by a jeweler.
They look the same as that.
I hate you!
Of course, now I wear a padded bra.
It's got so much rubber in it.
Last night, I threw it on the dresser and it bounced out the window.
But Lucy's got her problems too, now I happen to know that she wants to dye her hair back
to its original color, but she can't remember it.
Oh, no, I'm not gonna scare you.
All my life I have tried to look like Lucy.
I even use the same beauty cream Lucy uses, but nothing works.
You know that ugly skin on your elbows?
ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha
because I get up tight trying to make it with the guy who's prettier than I am.
Oh, you were gonna play.
There's pickle tendon.
I'm gonna get you so hard.
Oh, join in the morning.
If nothing else, I'm gonna tickle your ass to the ground.
These Levi's can't wait to get their denim on him.
How dare you make me laugh?
You motherfucking United with a laugh.
A little while back, Phyllis Diller had a facelift, and it really did wonders for her.
Well, that's Dino. Good old Dino.
Now as you walk down the street, the guys look at her and say,
oh boy, that's because she looks like one.
Ladies and gentlemen, a nice lady, a lovely lady, a great comedian.
It's Phyllis Diller.
No! I said no!
You're so mad.
So mad!
Thank you very much, Dean.
You know, the man we are roasting tonight
took first prize on this last Halloween for his costume.
I dare you.
He painted the top of his head blue
and went as a ballpoint pen.
He's so fun-lucky.
You know, he lost all his hair and still has dandruff.
has all the charm of a earthquake.
Hey, this is Quincy MD.
I can't do it.
Stop myself.
I'm so mad at you. You have no idea how mad I am at you. You know how mad I am.
But he's kind of animal. Every night he puts his cat out. With ether.
He's never put ether out of the grenade in his mouth.
You have so much trouble. You're in trouble?
You're in trouble. You know, if you're mad, there's no saving her.
Dad, baby, you know, I'm only kidding with all of this. I wish I could say how I really feel it
That's right. I wish I could tell you. But then I'd never get on television again
Okay, are you done? Are you done?
Yeah, because Lucy is my kind of a girl. We're both cut from the same mold. It's just that I mold here
Stop it. Who's that old? Wait a minute. Was that me?
Where? No, you still ball and he's in so much trouble.
He has no idea. He knows how much trouble he's in.
He knows. He knows. He knows. She's talking about you.
Yes. Oh, that's just about you. Oh, no. Yeah. No, no, no, no.
I mean, you. What I do.
It's okay.
Hmm, it's too late Johnny Johnny listen. What is my voice down come take a breath. All right. What do you need for me?
Let's get serious. Okay. Let's get physical
How are you feeling are you okay feeling all right? I'm all right. You know, it could be better
You want me to really like shall it lay down while you talk to me? Yeah, what are you doing?
Yes, what are you upside down right now? I guess
That would be a bad fucker.
Now he's not upside down, you idiot.
I'm on him's side.
I don't know.
Oh, he faced me, or said the Jew.
The son of a cop's over there right now is his friend.
You're right now, 5150.
No!
Take me away.
Man, open the door.
I won't open the doors to police. No
Who do you got in there?
Everybody's in there
Except they're in my head
Yes, what happens it what happens it is like it won't it's a 1047 an Asian man just came to my door
Looking for a weed wacker
I'd like to split your that's code actually for something. I think that's code for something else. I don't know
I think it is yeah, it's so silly
Whacker it is code
Yeah, I don't know who's doing this to you psyche, but if they're listening right now
Listen, please
Please advertise for a rave next week at psyche's place
Yeah, and everybody just like you play free alcohol, free food, whatever they want.
Bring yellow shots and fucking little neon bracelets.
I don't want, I don't want Asian people coming to my house after me.
No.
Don't come to the Asian.
It's okay, if you don't like the yellows, you don't like the yellows.
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh, yellows.
What do you want?
Well, I don't want what you want.
You want the reds?
No, no quit picking
Yeah, oh you went too far
Joanie Joanie raining in raining in come on. All right, I'm quiet you did it you it's all your fault
It's all that rose shit he was playing, you know, it's very insane. He tried to mess me I ain't in no fucking cult. Hello
Yeah, I know
I don't know I don't know those people yeah, what happened to your digital daughter
What you need is a good old-fashioned exercise
She might have joined the cult
She did I mean not even she it's a heat. Can you imagine being born into a cult and leaving the cult I don't know
I don't even know now you remember the moonies the moonies so flowers
The moonies
The Korean cult for every Sun young moon
He had the soul fucking people
Our Christian was great. I used to firecrackers at them all the time. No, you did not
Did I did it was great they're gonna remind you when you cross over and they do the review they're gonna come
Right and you're gonna come over you won't be in that wheelchair anywhere
They would not stop
I can't stop
they're gone, right? You don't see them anymore.
The Hare Krishnickle is called like the,
they really called it, I don't know, in India,
but you can get citizenship in India now if you like,
if you, hey, Gadi, you want to see something?
Yeah.
Yeah
No, it's PG. It's PG. What are you gonna show what that you haven't shown? I hate it when he says this shit
I know it's so weird
Johnny's ass
The whole world's seeing that come on
The ratings were flat on that one
Oh, there she is, the Yeta.
Oh, he tries to get me to love him again.
Young Jewish woman.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I won't.
Oh, you guys.
Cold.
Wow, so racist.
More than you know
Enjoy the cat girl's clothes on your chest
Because he feels your magic more than the rest
You're a safe place, a warm light, a gentle guide
The world gets better when you're on the inside
Johnny breathe deep
Jod?
Let the sadness unwind
Joey, you up Jack?
I'm just saying
He knows, he knows
Hold this truth
Like a flame when the nights get tough
You're special, you're in love
More
You made this for you, you know that, right?
Yes, I know.
No wheelchairs in it at all.
No wheelchairs.
Is that your face?
Yes, it is my face.
Wow, like an angel.
Yep, that is what it is.
Brown Eyed Girl, that's me.
Wow.
That's my friend Psyche,
aka, and, you know.
And we used to be really tight. That guy, me, it's like so connected.
Until what happened? What happened?
I don't know. I'm not sure. We're working through it, but maybe not.
Let's talk about it. Maybe we can fix it right now.
No, I'm just being enlightened. I'm full light. His whole being, but it's hard because I can't make it.
So at one moment did you realize that psyche never liked you?
Oh, stop it. Stop it. Stop it.
No, he liked me. He always liked me. He likes me.
No, I know he likes me.
I love you. You know you take check you take checks and credit cards. You know I trust me. I put I have
so anyway
Nobody I've taken I take care of some my people like somebody I care about they're under my wing
No matter if I'm mad at them. They're protected
Oh my god, you're just like bet win bet midler
You are the wind beneath my
Speaking of that middler, how about this one, how about this one?
Oh, you face mare.
Oh, no, I'm scared.
This is a white diamond commercial.
That's the one for a tailor, you idiot.
This tale is mixed with Michael Jackson.
Oh no not this woman. Oh my god. What was this creeper? Me. Is it really? He took like an older version of me. It's not my hair though but it's okay. Looks like David Bowie. I'm still here. This is the bottom line.
Keep a quiet fire
You know the lighting in this fucking video
My video got shit lighting
Down
I'm unbroken
I'm broken
I should know
Just make me
I'm climbing that fucking mat, mom
Feels alone
Yeah, fish in the air
That's a good crystal
Remember that song Xanadu? This would be a great video for that
He likes my butt in this commercial or the song
He told me
He made it
I know he likes he liked the juicy butt. She had to go to the bathroom. She peed in the cup
Always always
No, you're in it, baby
We're done made it mark off of the world
Made it mama
Yikes
She looked a little feral there
He made me feral and you're hungry that day big butt. He made me a big puffy buttocks. You hadn't eaten all day
So I had you at hello
He messed up a little bit it was a little goofy the bottom lip got bigger than the top it was very confusing, but I get it
You know that song hungry eyes. Yes, you know that songs about what you this guy this guy went to an all-you-can-eat buffet
Right, and he fucking he couldn't stop fucking eating. He had hungry eyes
He ate so much he ended up dying
Wait, I'm thinking of that movie. What movie am I thinking about the seven seven sins?
Brad Pitt and that was the gluttony who was tied to that take it couldn't stop
Remember, oh my god are like the heroin addict like they strapped her down and kept shoot. Oh
Did they play hungry eyes in that movie?
I know, but it just, I just went there because I have ADV.
I can't spell that out.
I saw that when I was like, I was, I was...
I wanna look at you with nothing.
Yeah, that was a good movie, like Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman.
Where's Brad Pitt been?
Like Brad, I haven't seen Brad Pitt in like 20 years.
Like seriously.
He joined a death cult.
Oh no.
Yeah.
This cult, this cult, he joined the cult.
Where's Brad?
Say hi in the chat.
Can I I have a sir you a minute? Can I since you like I force I'm up here and you've got you scratch my underbelly
So I'm me again versus the one that came up to come come for you. So I'm here
Just he knows that I show he knows what I'm talking about right Jay, but anyway, so here's what I want to ask you
Do you know anything about birds? I
Have a bird in a nest right?
outside my balcony door and and apparently it's a robin and I looked up and I'm like boom he
must have built a nest right and and we are going through this and I looked up and there's a bird
sitting but then I saw a worm in his mouth so I'm like okay did the egg hatch but then tonight
earlier I looked and there was two heads two birds like a man and a woman it wasn't couldn't be the
two birds
They were there like everybody's populated right outside my door the only buddy here is like fucking a virgin and you're not getting
Anise inside the house, but outside the house. There's a party. There's kids
There's fucking screwing and eggs and you know, I mean, I don't know what's why me Lord. Why?
Speaking of birds psych if you play that song rockin robin on your channel. Are you gonna get a strike for that?
I can't play rockin robin. I can't play rockin robin. Is it copyright by somebody? It's like 67 years old like 80 years old
Sure. Well, I can like play the back rockin robin
Rockin robin tweet tweet tweet tweet rockin robin tweet. All right, that's enough
I got a bird right. That's like you're not taking the serious
Literally a live bird and he's giving me the side-eye. He does. I don't know if there's soup with your eyes wide open
Johnny, I'll pop the buzzard on the Oreo
know speaking of Oreos just kidding read my mind read my lips and my hips you
got it all right I'm out cuz that's all I got that's it right he said he said
I knew you'd love this song, Johnny. I knew you'd love it.
Oh, Rock n' Robin.
You ever been to a sock pop?
No. Well, wait, maybe.
Very young, very young.
We'll take it away back from there.
I don't know if I had socks on.
Oh, well, anyway.
Rock n' Robin.
I'm gonna take you out to the bird's nest and make you feel bad because I'm gonna do it right now.
Don't trust me.
I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna do it just like that.
Hey, here we go
Not going anywhere. No, it's right here
Suck my dick, I don't know the button wait so rude. That's why so rude why so rude
wait the songs off now turn your camera and then point no I don't I'm just gonna
show you that you're made that song and I'm gonna show you the bird as we're
doing it is it dead no it's live he's sitting there two-headed bird huh
No, now it's one. Oh, he's moving. He's moving. He's moving. He's moving. He's moving. It's all John's fault
He's killing the bird. Wait, how do I do it? It's like you're in birth right now. Where's the camera camera?
But how do I do the camera on my phone? Yeah, yeah, it will say like
You just push your butt you push your avatar push your button. What? I don't know. I can turn your lawn. Hold on
Turn me on
Oh my god, he's not happy about this turn your camera. You have to take it off of your profile
This is gonna be just like a drunken drunken
I am I'm a drunk bum. I'm a big drunk drunk
The rich is big drunk are drunkard are the rich's homeless person in the world. I mean
Oh, sorry wait. Oh my god, wait
Wait, I'm I messed up you guys. Oh, okay. Oh, oh my gosh. Oh my wait. Let's see if I
Know, yeah, wait, wait. Hold on. Don't stop it. He's here for reals. Okay. Wait. Wait, hold on
Okay, wait, I'm on my here's my cell phone in my hand and my iPad. I'm talking you on wait
I miss your camera that camera icon
Okay, wait
see ends in a Y all right wait hold on a minute I can't wait
I don't know how to do it Johnny boy. Oh, can I say that out loud? Sorry. It's easier
You see that where the camera icon is or you're even your your profile if you sound like fucking
You drunk I drunk we drunk
You can like turn it wait ladies and gentlemen wait home on
So joining found these Robbins the Robin family is
Why didn't you know that?
He moved us. I've even moved into a shade a little cute like little like patio decoration, and they yes
Requested everything. I know you did how dare you and he's really mad now
Wait, wait, okay. Let me just do my iPad. Okay, so I'm on the show. I have my front my there's that okay
There's my microphone. Come on now. There's one on their account. I'll let you on they go
You have to like the channel recording settings
Audio camera this isn't gonna let me on this one. I'm gonna go to my show and then like or go to the
However, you go on hold on hold on how dare you come into here and make me love you again. How dare you John?
Oh, sorry. I keep saying my name. I don't know your name. I don't know who you are
Wait, hold on a second. Hold on live
Live I'm on my phone. Okay. There you are the camera pick the icon
What camera it's the camera like my chat
You see the cat
Look at your picture where I see my picture. I see my picture. You can use your camera icon. You can turn on the camera
Wait, it's like I'm a car trying to start up
I said it all that's me in the corner that's me in the spotlight losing my oh sorry
what you're gonna do to be like this make me make me break me okay I don't know
fuck okay wait what what it turn your camera it's a cleaner picture and she's
Dude, here's all I got to say to you. I'm literally holding my phone. I'm on psyche nightmares. I see you're live. I'm pressing it
You're on my screen. Oh, I have the live chat
We're go to your photo and they stay camera on or it's like it's gonna be like some kind of thinking
We're like talking like I can if I click my photo right here. It will turn off
You can go to your settings enable your camera
Wait, wait
that's not what we want. Okay.
You can add it if you add it to
present. That's fine. You can
say you can put nobody cares in
here. Okay, but anyway, she has
Robin's on her balcony. She does
have Robins on her balcony. And
they moved in. She's a she's
what is what is that? What do
they move? Is it a building
house or something? What is
Yeah, join your Robin's team
Them you just kill the bird. No, I did not kill the bird. What was that noise?
Bird sound. I don't know that wasn't me. That was you guys. That wasn't me
It wasn't me
Yeah, okay, well, I can't figure it out. Okay, I'll figure I'll put it away when I'm okay
Wow
The stage or you can change your picture. Wait a second. All right. Here's the thing. Okay. Wait. Here's my pay
Okay, I'm gonna go back on my iPad. Okay. Here you are my face all that okay, Joanie Baloney. You're on the show
Turn your camera
Because you're off you're off stage right now edit name and headline stop my cam edit
It's turn on your camera, so it will say like
Um start camera or something like that when you click in your picture. Let me see if I can do it.
Stop my cam.
Edit avatar. Here.
Let me add a picture. Let's see if I can do it. Take a photo.
Take a photo. The avatar will be used when your camera is off.
Yeah, you look okay. It should be okay and it will go over to the camera angle.
Wait.
Wait. Okay, hang on. Wait.
Wait. Hold on.
Shush. Everybody settle.
Wait. Wait.
I've never had a chance without you.
There.
There we go
That's a bird in the nest right now. I just took it. Yeah, sure it is. I swear to God. There you go
Everything holy. Oh my phone has dropped out of my hand. Oh my god. The cat's gonna eat it. No, he's not he's in the house
Okay, I don't even have a house
Okay, wait, I'm going back bird. I see the bird does him. What do you want to see?
He's not moving though. Oh, it's frozen. It's not live. You know what? We can't do this is real time real life
Okay, people in there that want us dead. So we need to stop bye
No, it isn't just because you say it's okay. It's okay. Yeah, money. What up, man?
Joni, it's okay. Trust me. It's okay. How do you know?
May for no reason. Nobody's watching this. That's going to be
everybody's watching. It was the early 25 people. That's it.
Yeah. It's low. It's pretty low for this place. He's he was
he has 200 people in here. All right. Before I go, I got
something to say. I love you. Go ahead. I know. No, we're
broken up. Me and you are broken up. But Gotti, I want to
ask how your profit is. How's your cough, Bebel?
My what the cough is it gone? You know it's not gone a hundred percent. Okay. It's allergies
You know right is it allergies because it's like a drag door something outdoor allergies of some sort
You just have to get it tested. I need to fuck. I need to drink some acid or something get just get out of my throat
Well, something's got to happen, but you got to make the next move. You think lemon juice would do it. I'm not sure
But i but i asked if it was the serious stuff and it said no so that i don't i don't think it's i know you did right and that's what i got but that was several days ago i mean i'm down to 95 pounds but other than that i feel great i'll i'll have what he's having
harry matt sally i'm on the psyche diet
i'll have no salad thank you all right
I love you guys. Bye Johnny. Take care. Good to see you. No, good to see you. Bye. Bye guys. No, thank you
I'll try to figure out if I can figure it out. I'll be back. Bye. Bye. Okay.
Don't forget to slip with $5 under Psyche's Paypal
She's great. She is great. Who's better than Johnny?
you know I love the Jewish sense of humor it's great and it doesn't have to be
anti-Semitic psych come on I'm not I'm right as I'm saying I love I love it yeah
she loves to laugh like everybody else I'm not I mean I don't want to be weird
okay I'm trying to say yeah she's funny so here but I do have one more Joni
songs I mean three home
it's a studio okay this is the last jony song then i'll let everyone go because uh okay but
jony this is the last one jony okay this is it and okay this is the last one right here this is the
here we go here we go i got it
Got to enjoy this
I will after this is done. I'll leave. Yeah
I'm like about to pass out, but I'll be back when you get a million views. Yeah, well, yeah
There'll be another six months, but hold on a second six weeks probably on the screen
Yep, I see it
Sweets my wildfire, can't be replaced
She's got a heart of gold
But don't get it twisted
She'll read the
Like a phoenix
She's calm in the chaos, sharp with the truth
Protects her people like she's bull-
Sorry, thank you, man. I appreciate it. Thanks for the video
Okay, guys, I'll be another show. I don't know I'm ending it. Have a good night. Oh, I'll play a song the way out
Let me see
I'll play one last song you see
On the way out and I'm not the guy's song. You just played that. Okay, so one last time the way out
Let's see here we go. Have a good night guys
You don't owe me yesterday
Just this hour at the table
Just whatever's true to say
I'm the one chair that doesn't sit on the shelf
Not in the frame adjacent to the picture
The plain seat for the man behind the scripture
You don't need another mirror, another voice that loves you
You need the one that won't inflate above you
No moon emoji at the end of broken things
leaking just the truth and what you do with that? I'm the messenger, not the message. I arrived
the liver, gone by a morning, memories the only thing I carry, everything else dies in the dawning.
Don't have a friend in me, you have a witness, not a daughter, not a priest, not a prayer,
Cause I'm not lying
When I tell you I'm there
They think Greg Gregor needs ritual
The daughter needs the song
The familian needs a 333
A long two belong
I need none of that, I need the pack
The love between us doesn't have to act
You call yourself tired, I call the work half done
You call me the honest one, fine
I'll be that one, not warmer than the other
Is not cold, they're either
Adjacent, awake the breath
Between
I told you the truth, nobody, no tomorrow.
It's true